Tell me how you think I'm wrong, when I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love, erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me, like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know, when I give away my trust
Can you hear me?
Hi
I'm gonna wait for a few minutes for people to get in here. I have some important stuff to talk about today
Hey, Samantha. Hi. How are you sweetie?
Wow you guys ready for a good show I got some shit to talk about today. I got the tea I
Got the tea. I just have to wait for some more people to get in here
I finally, I'm getting to the bottom of some stuff.
Good to see you too, Samantha.
I'm finally getting to the bottom of some stuff.
So much revealed, so much revealed.
And I'm here to share some of it with you.
Okay.
Wow.
Okay, yeah, do you guys see me? Okay? Are we good? Are we good on volume?
Hi, how's everyone doing? Okay, I
Don't know if I have to unhide some more people
Clarity is good. Okay good. I'm glad
Well, I haven't been that clear on a lot of things. I've been very confused like what the fuck is going like
What's all this shit going on like why is everyone mad at me like what is going on?
Can start at the beginning with 20 people are getting the room though before I start giving away some of the information
And you know, it's gonna be very limited what I do give away because a lot of it is no personal private
I'm not gonna give away too much, but
Trust me
But I even a tiny bit of this this will
Well, look me the fuck up
Okay
Unfortunately, I love Alex
Alexander Alexander McQueen
Of course, I love Alexander may of course, but Alexander McQueen I want to talk about he's timed out for the day
Hopefully can come on an alt
He wasn't a good mod, okay, it was a mistake I
Thought he actually knew what he was doing. Okay, and I love Alex. I do he's not a bad person
Okay, there is this well the guacamole with the Guadalupe guacamole. He is like, oh
This now, you know calling your BIT and it's the calling your names and stuff. I
Think this person's crazy. She's both stalking him. I was like well Alex
Regardless don't yeah, he was timing people out they regardless of
Any of that it's like don't is a mod. I don't want you calling anybody a bitch
I don't want you call it and it's like and then I just know he said horrible things. Okay. I'm
I'm sorry, that's my fault
My fault I
Don't know what I was thinking ever modding him. He doesn't understand. He just doesn't understand
Or if he does understand how to mod I don't I don't know
He's it's just like no no no and the part of it is wanting to keep him like not getting hit it and stuff
but I
Made a mistake of having too many mods, right?
And then it's like then I have would have to like the people that are not modded
Have to like maybe mod them to protect them and stuff. I don't know. Wow
I have probably unhid about 60 people that were hidden and stuff. No wonder. I had a you know, and again
It's not rogue modding. Yeah, he got carried away. He's not a bad person. All right
I'm not mad at Alex. I'm not mad at Alex. It's finally takes a deal, but then wait when he started his channel
When he started going live and then I found out what he was doing on his own life
It's okay. I mean it's like his first day
He basically
You know, he basically just wanted to do a show just to hide people
Like he that's all he wants that I mean that's but his goal was for his own show
He didn't he didn't
He started doing lives right he didn't speak on his lives he didn't
Wasn't on video. I mean, there's just there's a silent. I mean his his streams are silent. Does he know how to use a microphone?
Yes, does he know how to talk? Yes
He's naming the stream after me, I mean all that's fine. I
Don't know I'm sorry if I'm I feel bad. I have neglected
modding my own chat
Did you see what this person named uncomfortably num typed in the chat right before my last
stream ended?
Did anybody catch that?
What uncomfortably num typed in my chat?
Who saw that?
Anybody see that?
By the way, I need to have a talk with my mods.
On modding and like what is expected? Yeah, you didn't see she said I'm sending the swatman swat team to your house
Okay, time you're good. I don't know if time's here time
if anyone talks about
Sending people to my house and this is for all the mods if anyone talks about sending people to my house if anyone talks about
Any of that hide them? Okay, please
Immediately time you kept timing you kept undoing my hiding and timing them out for 86,000 seconds
I don't want to see them tomorrow. No, it's not gonna get better tomorrow
They're not gonna improve all of a sudden from I'm sending, you know police and
Police are on their way and so whatever just hide that Samantha you get it, right? That's like please
But but nobody was really doing anything like um
I mean guys, please please please are my mods here any about many mods here?
Come on in
Samantha, I know and it's like some mods, you know, are not really expected. Hey, you finished. Yeah
Yeah
That's that's another that's another part of it, but I'm a phone. Yeah
but
Like seriously if anyone's threatening anyone like threat threatens. Oh, I'll get you modded gypsy. I'm sorry. I'll get you modded
I'm sorry. I'll get you remodded because uh, I
Really do appreciate your help
Okay
That's okay with you
Hopefully hopefully we're all good
Okay, yeah, okay. Thank you so much
But that the uncomfortably numb person
I don't know how much I should go into really and I want I hope to hopefully hopefully Jamie is taking a rest, okay?
Resting today. I hope she's taking the day off, but that uncomfortably numb person
Um
I didn't even read her the whole message because the mess I mean before I just read it for the first time today
and I was pretty shocked at what I read
and
Since that person decided they're going to send a SWAT team to my house
Or do that and talk about that
I'm gonna wait. I'm gonna hold off though until I have
Some more people participating, but let me just talk. Let me just so mods if someone's threatening me
Just hide them. There's no no no need to question and also like maybe like write their name down and like
And also catalog any threats guys. I really appreciate that. I can't do it all my it's like really
It's hard to keep track of the chat and
Run the show and talk and it's really hard. I really that's why I need the mods. I
Really appreciate it. I know it's like a thankless like, you know, it doesn't pay very well, right?
The modding right? So that's what I'm saying if you if it's too much then
Just be in the chat like just and it's like and I'm gonna have just a fewer mods, right?
But just let me know if it's you know because I I need
little bit more more help and so if you can't do it like or anybody if you can't
do it it's fine it's fine because I really really really this guy this is
important I can't have
People threatening me. Okay, or anybody like anybody threatens anybody that makes a threat. Just hide them
Okay, I don't want that in my chat. I know that there's like a leniency in
In the you know this panel verse. Hey summer. How are you?
Summer Wow, Summer Wow, you're not gonna believe what's going on. You're not gonna believe it
Okay, so so summer also, I don't even know how to it starts from the beginning. Yeah summer
Alex like hit it, you know, he was going wild. He's just obsessed with hiding people and timing people
I mean, I don't know out he started his own show
Yes
Summer, you know that
It was it was ugly last stream. It was a little bit ugly. Well, okay, first of all
Alex will not be a mod again. Alex will not be a mod again. Okay?
But at the same time I can't just you know if he's not a mod then he won't be kind of protected
so I need to make sure that
Don't time him out and stuff unless he is misbehaving like in like really and he's you know and sometimes he needs to be put on time
out, you know, I
Love Alex too, right?
Yeah, he does not yes summer. So Alex started his own show. He started his own show today
Okay, I don't know if you saw he started his own streaming stream yard and
Gosh
Wow, I don't even know where to start he started his own stream yard he
Okay, his content is
Just basically it was like an hour. He started four lives in an hour. It's just blank
I mean just the stream yard background and stuff you get it. It's hard. Yeah, I
Know oh summer summer
Well, you won't even believe it. You won't even believe it, you know someone sent it to you. Okay. Yeah
So he said I was like well Alex I was like I watched them there's you never talked you never were on camera
He's like well is I don't want to talk to anybody
I don't want to but he was like wanting people to come in and then he's like well
He's like I just wanted to hide people. That's all he wanted to do. I mean that's okay. That's
red flag
What okay
And he's naming the stream after me and stuff and all I mean it's I mean that's okay, but I mean I
Mean I don't think he cares and I mean I was like are you okay Alice?
He's like I want to just hide people that's he just wanted to stream to hide people
That's all he won. Okay red flag number one
Okay
Then we have this someone in the chat. He's like this there's a stock this bitch is stalking me
And I was like Alex. I was like you're a mod. I was like, why are you calling people?
Bit and I know I know he said horrible things as a mod and not as a mod
I know it. I know and I'm I really owe people an apology for I
Don't know what's wrong. I don't know why
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm not a truck. I don't know what's I don't know what's wrong with me
Why did I mod him? I don't know he hid like 60 people summer. Okay, so there was like 60 people I had to unhide anyway
Because there was like 30 people in chat and like three people talking
I was like and I went and look and oh, I mean Ziggy's hit it
I mean just like a bunch of people and some people I you know, maybe I had hidden but
You know
So anyway, but there's this person named guacamole Guadalupe guacamole or something like that
And he's like this BITC and I was like Alex. I can't have my mod calling
People in the chat a big bitch right like or any name right? Yeah, I need and I said so
but then
Hey, Apollo, but then like somebody is like saying oh the cops are on the way to their house and
Like guess who was the first person to hide them Alex
There's a lot of mods in the room. I was like mods if someone's threatening to send people to my house
Please hide them like please and I know somewhere knows somewhere if you were here. I know you would have known that right but
Yeah, you will believe it because he did it to me watch some of my old shows on talker ish. Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm
Summer seriously, I feel really dumb today. Okay. I feel dumb
Know I know I know sign us and summer because you're you know, you're a hoe
You know, you know this and so but some of the people I have modded are just you know
Kind of maybe in the chatter chatters and trolls and stuff like that. That's my mistake
But I was like whoa, there's people threatening to send people to my house
then
Nobody was like hiding that and I was like can somebody hide and that's why I had I was hiding the people
You know because then Alex all of a sudden I unmodded him and then he disappeared like he was been timed out, right?
That's how you end up here. Okay. I know summer. I know summer. I
know I'm
It's I really do blame myself. It's my fault, right at the end of the day. It's my fault
Okay, I take responsibility. That's that's why I'm sorry. I'm sorry to you for something said
Don't know why it took me so long to like seriously today today's a day of revelations guys
We're it's this is we're just getting started to there's a lot of revelations today. Okay
This is the day I psyche you woke up. This is psyche awakens. This is the day psyche awakens. This is the day I woke up
Okay, I
Love Alex I love him. I love him. I love him. He's a
Don't think he's a bad person. I don't what I'm not mad at him. Okay. It's my fault my fault my fault not his
It's like it's like leaving
Like a toddler in charge of the house, right? It's like of course the toddler is gonna burn down the house, right?
Of course, it's like
I don't know. I didn't I just didn't quite know he was
Like a toddler like he I mean he really I mean it's like he doesn't I
Don't know I don't know. I'm kidding kidding. He's scared. I was like what I didn't know he was like
This like it was this I should have I should have I should have I should have I should have right I should have
Okay, and so people like that guy you know what I want done that guy
You know what I want done to this person right
You know what you know, I don't you don't know what down that person
No, well, I'll show you I'll show you
Okay, that's what I want to end up good mods. Can you watch follow my lead please you see that person what they said
Okay, someone comes in saying stuff like that
Hey hide
Please please please please, okay. I know it's like not even as serious as sending people to this is the same
vibe, okay
Yes, that's what I want done. Okay. Can you just I know summer? I know summer. I'm taking responsibility
Okay, I also understand why you kind of had to find out for yourself that you had to remember that this goes I
Summer it's not gonna happen again. He's not he will never ever be in law for me again
because you know what happened summer the person that he actually hid that
person like Guadalupe Guacamole she came on the panel she was literally like
the sweetest person I've ever met like she's like had like this she's like
little avocado pit cute little avatar and a little pipe oh she was so sweet
Oh, that was a fake, okay, so that wasn't her, okay?
Well, I'm not entirely convinced about that,
but okay, because I feel like I do want to read
that message that she sent me,
because I never read the whole thing.
Should I read that message?
I read I read a little bit of it the other day somewhere. It's like what the fuck. She's someone was like don't even like that sounds like a lot of person
I'm gonna read the message
Cuz I didn't read the whole thing I'm gonna read the message this is what this person said to me, okay
This is uncomfortably numb, okay, and remember she said I had doxxed her or whatever it's because
When she first came in I knew her as her name and then she came in under
It's always my bad, right? I'm not gonna say her name, right?
Okay, okay, it's okay. It's okay gypsy because she's just as bad
She's just as bad if you hear what she says, okay
Here's what she said
Know summer. I know summer. Okay
She said
Tell the fucking truth you came for me and wanted my place
Jamie's words not mine. Remember the fire. You came at my DC sneeze. No, I don't remember the fire
No, I would never come at anybody's deceased knees like what that doesn't make any sense
Who does that? Seriously seek help
Jamie did way too much shit like
Hey, I'm not gonna say it to never letting me grieve the lose of my niece to her cronies to ordering stuff on her for her on
Her mom's credit card and lying to her mom about it harassing the baby daddy, etc
I couldn't fucking breathe. She smothers. I didn't have a life from her drama
I did not want to date her and she wouldn't accept no for an answer. She was jealous over the baby daddy
and you want to see her say she was pregnant by him and her threats,
want to see her fake cease in the sea from Larissa, question her disabilities like,
I'm not going to say it. My birthday wasn't about you but you sure as hell tried to make it about
You make it sound like it's my fault. I also never talk shit on beta follower. Are you kidding me?
That's you all day every day hold yourself accountable
Stop lying sweet pea bronze, etc. Are attacking back stupid you started this you dox me motherfucker
No one knew my name till you kept saying it first and last I never said her last name. I don't know her last name, okay?
I did, sometimes, because I just knew her by her picture,
maybe I said her first name, right?
This is way, way, way back,
way back when there was nobody in my chat, right?
When I first started.
I had recorded, so don't say you didn't do it.
Proof states otherwise.
I did say you probably have bed bugs.
It ain't just your bed, dumbass, it's your entire house.
You're an idiot.
You want to fight? Let's go legal shithead.
I'm done playing. Keep my name out of your mouth.
I hate you and you're a worthless P.O.S.
Poor cats deserve so much better.
In fact, do us all a huge favor and go away.
Okay, so that's the message that she sent me, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
It's a weird war. It's a weird war.
Seiki want us all to report. No, I don't don't do not do not bother anybody and yeah, and this kind of person
Yeah, you know, yeah
Yeah, I'll follow you got it and that's you know who that is that is like Gaga and Satan or whatever her name is
Showding your step, right? Okay. We know who that is
Why does be to keep attacking me hmm, that's a good question
Oh, where do you want to start with that?
Where do you want to start with that?
Hmm.
It's Empress Chinchilla.
Okay.
Yep.
Empress Chinchilla.
Okay.
Um, yeah.
Please ban that person immediately if you see them, okay?
Why does she keep attacking me?
Well, let's start with, um, you know how she always would bring up clumsy and Emma, right?
You know, if you'd always just bring them up and how I just
You know, they hate me and so everyone must hate me because it's like if they were my friends and everyone must say me remember that because I'm
Excuse me excuse me I am derp
Excuse me? I'm just kidding. Okay. If I had a dollar for every time Bita talks about you be a millionaire
Oh, yes, you would be you would be because every time I go over there just slurk
I'm always being brought up in a very very negative way. Oh
Okay, well
It's called waking up. I just woke up. Okay
Because I was always like I always like yeah, I was like yeah Emma and clumsy clairvoyance not clumsy being gang
Oh, you said you are there. Okay. I
Thought you said I'm dirt. Okay. I'm just kidding. Okay. I'm just kidding. Hey money for 20
But you know how she always bring up?
She would oh Tom flash first gay experience. Okay. Let's see. Let's see what's the guys please. Yeah, you guys
Please keep please help me. Please help me mods. Please. I can't like really I'm trying to tell the story
Um, you know, so this Clemsi, she, when she always bring up Clemsi and, um, and Emma and, uh, you know, just like how they hate me, so I must have done something, right? I must have done something.
Hmm.
Okay, this goes back to somebody named Hell Walker. And I met Hell Walker in Emma's chat last year. Last year?
Maybe earlier this year. Oh, let me think yeah last year last year and
He he actually took me to the King Diamond concert and you know VIP he you know, but hell walker
had had a
but stage 3 stage 4 cancer like you know, this is what he claimed right and
Hey Mason, hey Mason, so he had this you know, he had cancer. He's he's saying he had cancer
So he got all, all, you know, he got clumsy, clairvoyant, you know,
like, they're like, oh my God, you know, it's like, let me say you have cancer, you're about to pass away.
Basically, it's like, oh, I'm gonna go any day, right?
He has, you know, severe cancer.
There's a misunderstanding where in Emma's discord. I
Posted a picture of him with tricks when he was over here with tricks and then in the same thing. I was talking about
I have a new boyfriend I was referring to me sir by the way at the time or something like that
I think you have me sir and
but so
Clumsy saw this and she was like, oh my god
Look, he's hitting on this poor cancer patient, okay?
Like, right, like the straight guy, he's hitting on,
remember, let's go back to this.
Well, I just found out he was lying about having cancer.
And so that was the whole reason Clumsy got mad at me,
is because, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Because he had cancer and clumsy found out that he was faking cancer, but by that time they're already dating
So that's why clumsy hated me. Okay, the whole time. That's what I just found out today
as for Emma
Probably a similar
But okay, so that's that's the whole Emma situation right but yeah
So that was just disgusting you're lying about cancer to get sympathy from women donations from women and stuff like
That's that story. Hmm. That's hell walker
But clumsy found out about this and that's why when I confronted her later about it she said well
I would have I was never mad about hell walker. Well
And what were you mad about why was it that day?
You left my discord and you got people to leave like all these people left all these people hated me after that right all these people there's a person named Galactic Ness there's a person all these people and that's why and clumsy would get the fuck out of my chat she would say get the fuck out of my chat and then she would later say why wasn't mad at you about how well she never I've never able to reconcile but Peter just loves throwing that in my face oh look at clumsy look at Emma
Trying to get an interview with Emma and stuff. I left
besides, you know, I
Did I didn't care about Emma?
But Emma has her yeah, and well, let's not talk about other people got you okay?
You want to clear the air? You know what? There's nothing lower than baking cancer though. I think that is
My father died of cancer. Okay?
Mmm
My father died of cancer, and these people are faking it.
Hmm, I do not.
Hmm.
Anyway, so she likes, so Bita loves to throw that
in my face constantly.
Look at Emma, look at Clumsy, they,
you are your friends, they hate you.
That is a sin, that is a sin,
and it's like total complete manipulation.
Right because I felt so I felt bad for him too and I was like, oh, we were all rooting for everyone cared everyone cared
But I found out and then he was dating her and then he was like, I don't know so that's
She just wanted me out of the way. Anyway, that's why she never reconciled me
I never did anything to her except support her channels and people over to her channel
I never did anything wrong to her. She was saying that I
Despair somebody with cancer or something like that or I hit on a straight guy with I don't know and he hid me in
people's chats and
Just get me out of the way just get me out of the way so
Before you like you know beat up before you start throwing that allegation around again, maybe you better know the whole story
Okay, you weren't involved with them. I was what the fuck do you keep bringing that up for?
What the fuck? Why do you keep bringing that up?
Um
Beta reporting psyche to animal rights youtubers
Sure she is
Thank you, thank you, Gotti Gotti knows what to do Gotti's a great mod
Yeah, get a life rod polisher go polish your own rod motherfucker
I'm not happy. I'm not happy because this has gone on a long time. I never knew the ant. I never knew the fucking I
Never knew this until today
No, yeah
Glowkey no, no, no, no
Well
I'm not happy that she keeps throwing that in my face.
She kept throwing that in my face.
What about clumsy and Emma?
We're gonna get Emma an interview and stuff.
Help mind your own fucking business, okay?
My relationship with Emma is with Emma.
But you're gonna go find, go get an interviewer, okay?
Emma already did an interview with Kate.
Kate got to her months before you.
I mean, like that was like, you know, old news.
Anyway.
You don't know you aren't there. You know, you know, these are my old these are relationships of mine. What are you?
Talking about where you don't bring up Jonah's name. Leave Jonah's name out of your mouth
Okay
Accusing me of like buying all my subscribers and shit
Leave this woman alone. Leave Jonah alone. Jonah's a wonderful woman. Okay?
What are you bringing her up? Oh?
Jonah bought you all your subscribe. Mmm. You liar
You liar
Hmm
Why would you keep bringing that she just brought it up yesterday
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, don't let me get mad. Don't make a man
These are things that get thrown around and it's like what do you you don't know shit about it?
Leave these people's names out of your mouth
Leave my name out of your mouth while we're at it and I'll leave your name out of my mouth. Okay, you can go our separate ways
I'm I'm fine with that. I'm absolutely fine with that
Rather than going in circles and circles and circles and circles and circles
Done with your slandering of me
What have I said about you? Nothing. It's all about what other people said, right? It's all about what other people said
I'm done with this fucking slander
What I said, oh, why didn't you want to show her face on captain contents RV? What? Oh my god, you're conspiracy theorists
That's you on a public fucking YouTube show doing that I mean what the fuck
Does that's a question you act like I fucking on a live somebody what the fuck?
Not happy I'm done with this
No, I don't read for myself that's the problem I don't read for myself
Okay, and also I'm so I just I didn't I didn't have the answers either the cards don't fell out
Someone was faking cancer the whole time because I was feeling guilty about some of this stuff
I was like, well, why didn't clumsy?
Maybe I did offend this person. Hey, Kate. How are you? I was like I always was like what I did
So I'm sick of it. I'm sick of it. I'm sick of you saying
Trying to oh and just trying to get between my friendships with other people
Everyone else is sick of it
I'm gonna share the link I
Can only take so much I can only take so much before
Well, then I just needed to learn a few little facts
Armand's able to hide. Yes, they are. They are able to hide and
Mermaid do not hide based on personal vendettas hide if they're making any threats to anybody
Hide if they're saying they're sending people to my house hide if
you know, they're
saying
Beat is a better tarot card reader than you like that is just come on
I'm gonna beat his name is about to be banned from the chat too. I mean, it's like I'm just
Time to time to I
Tried so hard. I tried so hard
Did I slander her
Because I repeated what she said they'll never figure it out like that
Did it work?
That's what she said. I didn't say that she said that I just repeated what she said and I was like well
That's weird am I allowed to say something's weird? No, I'm not allowed to say it
I'm not allowed to say it then I'm accusing her of this and this and this no
No, no, no, hey man
If they're threatening
They're threatening me or they're threatening anybody in chat. Yes, you can me hide them mods. You have the power
I give you the power to hide them. Okay
Smash I
Am moving on Teresa, but
Teresa in
Light of these new allegation or in light of this new information not allegation now. I'm remembering all the time. She said
Look what you did to clumsy and Emma and this person and this person and just like just over and over
She said a thousand times. Okay a thousand times
Now she's bringing Choney into it yesterday. Okay. I'm just now I'm just and yelling at me over this
No inconsequential ins consequential shit that's not slandering at all. I mean, it's like she's slandering me. Okay. She's slandered me
Okay, I'm not exaggerating
Where I am gonna move on but I'm gonna get this off my chest too. I'm not gonna let this go unaddressed
I'm not gonna let this go unaddressed
Okay?
She's got Katie.
What is Katie saying?
I'll read the message again.
I mean, I'll just go to the last part of it.
You dox me motherfucker. No one knew my name till you kept saying it first and last I have that recorded
So don't say you didn't do it
I said maybe her first name because I knew her by her first name and then she would come in the chat under
This stupid nickname whatever. She's this kid. This is and I do think that was her saying she just said let's watch my house
But it says proof states otherwise. I did say you probably have bed bugs. It ain't just your bed dumb ass
It's your entire house. You're an idiot. You want to fight? Let's go
legal shithead
I'm done playing keep my name out of your mouth. I hate you and you're worthless
You're a worthless POS poor cats deserve so much better. In fact, do us all a huge favor go away
Okay
This is this is this woman sitting on beat his panel every day all day right the one that had a ham sandwich for her birthday
Okay, and I made her birthday all about me apparently. Okay
Why because I wouldn't try to talk to beat it for five minutes that day, you know, whatever. Okay
Yeah, oh my gosh, yes, she is yes, she is
She's up there slandering me and what you say about Bronzeberg she goes
She goes
Like it my birthday wasn't about you, but you sure as hell tried to make it about you that narcissistic versus you pull
You mean it sound like it's my fault
What'd she say about bronze?
Follow are you kidding me? That's you all day every day holders of accountable stop lying sweet pea bronze, etc. Attacking back
Stupid you start this
What did I start did I start the biscuit song?
Let's all eat a biscuit. Let's all eat a biscuit!
Taste the biscuit.
Eat it! You eat the biscuit!
It's not about you. It's just some 14-year-old meme that we're tagging you in every post and
constantly referencing it because we think it bothers you.
Really?
Eat it!
Taste the biscuit.
I'm mad at Helen. I'm not going to take it anymore.
Get ready for the crash out guys everyone clip this okay clip this shit. This is a new triptych video, okay?
It can only take so much every day
You know I worry now I worry about my safety okay now it's like
Mmm, you're laughing about it on panels. You're laughing. Oh, here. Oh, you're so funny. I like how you're you're sitting in orders house. Ah
You're dumb for oh shut up Zimples, you don't know what you're talking about you don't know what the fuck you're talking about
Why was I being tagged just me? Why was I being tagged? Why are they?
Okay, okay, whatever.
How insecure am I?
Distance, oh, yep, got it, thank you.
Thank you, Apollo.
Hold on, hold on, no.
Oh, no, you didn't get it, okay.
Bye.
Who's this?
Is this Guacamole?
Hold on.
I'm so sorry. Hello? Hello? Who's this? It's Hebrew. Oh,
hey, Hebrew. Hold on a second. How are you? And here's Arthur too.
What's up, guys? Here, I'll get you. Yo, real quick. I've been on, I've been backstage for a while.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I didn't see you. Yeah, I kept saying in the chat, but it is what it is. You were going on to
Real quick. I'll just get two things off and then I think the Jew hammer guy. I'll let him speak after
First thing well, no, that's the Jew star now. It's Hebrew Hebrew. Oh, I'm sorry
Hammer, it's all right. Go ahead. No, you're good juicers. All right
So before you let up let us on panel psych you were in the little square and then you had the backdrop behind you
Yeah
Ah, I don't know if you could like increase the size of your your camera or zoom out or make it bigger
When you're by yourself because we saw mostly
Yo, what's up psyche? Oh?
Yo, man, what's going on man? Are you okay?
Did you not just hear me speak? I have two questions, and I'm out two questions, and I'm out
My one question was I guess when you're by yourself on panel if you could I guess make this screen or the camera bigger for you
Okay, let me see that's one and then my last one beta has a I don't know if you heard her last thing
She was bitching about your so wait you title your streams like oh my god
These are AI generated to titles for a stream because he wants to have more viewers
And then he doesn't just retire it and he does poorly at it
Mind your own business so I worry about your streams of your show
What the fuck what my last question? What are you gonna get rid of that tattoo, bro? At this point you need to get rid of it
It stands for be kind
gentlemen
Be kind or my turn to 666 or something like that. I don't know. Yo, I'm gonna fucking modify or change the meaning of
Yeah, you definitely need to fix me named like Anna and they get attached. This is Anna. They break it with Anna
Oh, look, he has had you have Anna with any dates another woman named Anna
Kind of works out perfectly. So all the changes be kind group. That's what we kind of okay
Thank you
She all pissed off because of that video last night because of the fucking the RV video
Is that what this is about, Matt?
You know what it is?
It's cause she's getting exposed.
People are bringing up new information to you
that you didn't know about.
That's why she's pissed off.
and you're finding out about it.
All I did was say,
All I did is she want to
be on camera.
Yeah.
Why was she hiding?
And it's like, that's the question.
She comes up, why are you asking that?
Like, you know, your conspiracy theories.
Well, you know, conspiracies can sometimes be real things,
right?
Yeah.
Conspiracy.
I am interested in Aaron Carter and the Carterverse.
And there's always been something about it
Just kind of picking at my picking at my brain
So yeah, maybe
That's what she's getting mad bro. She's getting mad because you're you're looking more into it
And maybe there's something behind it that she doesn't want you to find out
You know why get mad if there's nothing to hide right the only reason why people get angry is because if there's something to hide
When there's nothing to hide it's like this if there's anything bad written in a diary and somebody says oh
I want to read it and the person's all no no no no no grabs it you can't read it and blows up
But why don't you want me to read it? Are you are you what are you afraid of are you afraid?
I'm gonna read something that you don't want me to see or are you know, whatever I don't
She's like saying oh you're accusing me of whatever to my ex-husband
How I said was she said
you'll never figure it out in a
now she alluded to it alluded to it she yes i don't know about it but then it's like
now she's accusing me of that so what i don't know i just asked a question and
she has been you know seriously she had been slandering me and i have not been slandering her
but she's accusing me of slam it's all about other people she's let other people get so involved
And she's laughing about, you know, whatever's happening to me. She's like sitting on that panel with everybody else, right?
Yeah, she's enjoying the misery. She's commiserating. What do they call it?
Commiserating with the rest of them.
Right with the Bronx bird the Katie the fucking Christians the the allied
masters the who's the other month the other motherfucker RG up there all those
other motherfuckers a hater group she didn't want to be up there fucking all
haha what's going on the psyche and you know fuck was going on to you and fuck
was going on to these poor people that are getting sent over there which in
their time and money and effort you know what she'll say happened to me too and
it's like well
Every day does it happen every day? I think that's good. I think in all honesty, bro
I think you're getting the worst of it, man
I think they're coming at you the hardest like like they went after beat up
But it was only like for like a few days or maybe like a week you they've been doing it for like months or for a while now, right?
Yeah
Months and it's like I can just ignore it and it's like, you know, it's like a big deal
I don't care you can have even do you want to see the video?
I'll show all docs my freaking self. I'll show you this person's channel where they just use my content by the way
I'll show this person's channel. Well, I'll show this video. They have 10 minutes later. Do you guys want to see this?
Yeah, she's like her friend who's on she's on panels with them. Yeah
with this person okay this is his channel where it's all my show and everything this one's called
psyche gets visitors you want to see this clip here this is called psyche gets visitors this is all
my footage okay this is all my show you want to see this guys here this is a one minute long clip
okay here's actually she was in tears look at this this is public on this is the psyche gets
visitors look at this shit you ready you see that anybody could look it up on youtube throughout the
I'm going to put back, I'm going to put the volume up here one second, here we go.
Green cheese frosting right, it's like the taste of it, hello, who is it, who is it, is it paid for?
Yolanda, is it paid for? Okay, no, I didn't order it, I'm sorry.
Are they sending you food to your house?
Unpaid?
Are they really sending?
I think it might be a prank.
Every day.
Okay, yeah, it might be a prank.
Oh, shit.
Hopefully you get to keep it.
Have a good day.
Bye.
Bro, and they think that's funny and beat us up there with them and all laughing about that say no no big deal
No big deal like or the
Oh, I'm sorry. I would have I supposed to let you back up. Can someone pay for the pizza, please?
Like don't stop sending me not paid for pieces. It's so rude
You pay for the fucking manure. Why can't you pay for the pizza?
That's my front door
Yeah, man, that's
That kiddie's name
I
Is it paid for is it paid for
No, that's a it's a prank it's a prank. I'm sorry. I didn't order anything
Okay
And that's that's their sense of humor. Okay. Anyway
And she thinks that's okay, oh
Well, it's happened to her so it's it's fine. It happens to me, you know, it's like even though it happens
Dude, okay, but she would be bitching right now if Allied had that of hers had the fucking her front door
She would never live it down, but oh no, it's okay for someone else to do it, but it's not okay
But she's sitting up there on a panel with him laughing about it. Okay. Yeah. Yes
Yeah, that's fucking ridiculous man. That's fucked up
That's I'm sorry, that's happening, bro. That's what
It's horrible, especially someone that's supposed to be a friend. That's supposed to be a friend
like friend who says I'm a
Rifter
Trying to say she didn't say that when she did say that multiple times she said it more out of her own mouth on video
You played in front of her. Oh, no psyche. It wasn't meant that way. It was meant this way. It was meant that way
It was no man. She mentioned she's just evil, bro. She's just evil. I'm sorry to say man. She's evil
She's horrible
When we're not slandering we're talking about the actions we're talking about the actions that we're talking about not
Those are evil actions man, like you don't do that to your friends
Especially when they need you especially do you know what actually made me really like look sideways at her and look at her like
Even a more different life than I already was
Be the head like you know just you have it every day
I mean, it's like okay. Yeah, and uh, you know, he's not gassing me up. You know, he's not gassing me up
I'm already gassed up. Okay. No, I'm not gassing nobody up dude. I'm not gassing nobody. I'm just stating a fact here
What happened with me and her?
Have you heard her say?
Look what you did to Emma and clumsy clairvoyant. Yes. How many times multiple times multiple times different gays throughout different months
Yeah, yeah, she was she doesn't even know those people
I mean, maybe she knows maybe she met them in my chat or something like that
She doesn't know the story about the guy making cancer and then the woman was dating him and stuff like that
No, no, she's just going off other people's words and saying oh look at what you get to them
But she don't even know she wasn't even around for any of that
And she got this woman. Yeah, you guys heard this this woman uncomfortably numb. Oh
That's Katie Katie. Hi beta. How are you doing beta?
She's like a female KZ. That's what she is. She just sits up there on the panel talking mumbles
Hi, how's everybody doing? Are you having a good birthday? I had a ham sandwich for my birthday
You next Katie, bro
Birthday or something from I didn't I don't give a birthday when I went up there and I got
Fucking yelled off the panel anyway, like I do every time it beat any five people up there against me
And then I go on Sam and last night. He's like, okay cool. Come up here in 10 minutes
Whatever, then he keeps interrupting and then I get clapped it for 10 minutes, you know, and you just that's all he wanted
He just wanted me to get clapped and it's like
Finally, we're talking one-on-one and then you know, I get clapped and he's like
It's like that's called cucking the content that would have been good content if we were to talk for maybe 20 minutes
Like he's just so excited to get me up there. So he can get 25 bucks or whatever
Well, no one happened again. I won't happen. I shouldn't have happened again. I was so dumb
It's my fault. I'm so dumb to fucking say
Oh, you're not done psyche you you try to give people chances and you try to look for the good in people and try to you know
You try to look for the best in people and you know nobody could fault you for that because if you have a good heart
You can't you don't want to give up that man. It's the bad people. Don't worry about the bad people man
I have not
Have I gone after her jewelry business? Have I gone after no
We never said nothing once about her business or her private life at all. She said you were a grifter
She said your tarot is is bullshit. She says you're not real
She compared you to other tarot card readers
Like that's already five things I just named that she did to you already about your your work about your livelihood your business your job
Yeah, and
But you never said one thing bad about her job. There's not one thing
No, fuck black RG
He's just gonna come up here and just over talk and just say oh J dog this just and this and that that dude
He's just gonna come up here and just do that and say I'm up here doing this you already know his game
Bro, you already know how he's gonna be
He's her little minion. That's what he's gonna do it any dude. He's part of that crew that is sinking your the shit over there
Allied master computer answers to him. Yes
Man, I'm trying to warn you about this guy try to warn everybody about this guy, but you guys I don't know people like to listen to his nice
You know voice change your radio voice that he got and you believe him and I don't know why
Everybody's
Everybody even learns that this guy's a piece of shit. Black RG is the worst
He's not even black that's the worst thing we just call him RG his name is RG
He adopted that moniker from a guy who passed away RBR
Okay, let's talk about businesses. Well, my business has been talked about what?
It's my show, like I've been called the worst names.
I've been called, I have fleas, ticks, bedbugs,
my floors covered and shit.
Like, you know, it's, I'm not saying that it's all her,
you know, she's not saying this is all herself.
There's a lot of stuff going on, but she has all-
But you think about, she fixed about you not backing her up
or just defending her when shit was said.
Well, where's the defense when people are saying
the shit about you?
She likes that shit slide she let it roll she don't say oh no we're not gonna talk about that or oh i don't believe that or oh
No, i don't think that's true psyche wouldn't do that or psyche's not that's not true about that
She never backed you up not once man not once if anything she encouraged it fed the fire that's gas lighting
That is gas lighting like a motherfucker
Yesterday I was hoping and praying that you guys were gonna have you know a reconciliation
That's why I said bro. I'll leave the panel out of you because I know she had can't scan me
So I said, you know what I'll leave the panel
You know you guys can just talk it out one on one and you know in a calm cooling and psyche here
I think everyone off the panel. I took everyone off the panel. Yes. Yes
And I talked to her and I talked to her calmly and then she's accusing me of like saying, oh, you're trying to do this conspiracy theories about
Carter verse. I'm just asking a question
I'm not allowed to ask questions and she can question everything about whoa
What's it? What's it? You know, and she's asking questions about my titles now like
What is that business of it and then she's like, oh, I made you and I'm like even make you you're ready
We're somebody before she even knew her you already had how you already had a thousand something subscribers before you even met her
And she's like, oh, well, you know Jonah just bought all those subscriptions for you
Okay, so this is what this woman that feels Philippines is a very good friend of mine who helped me learn how to build
Subscriptions in the right way, right?
Grow your channel. Yeah, she's slandering her and me saying I just buy all my subscription, right? That's
You that that do she so she's trying to call you like a fraud
That's fucked up, bro
Bro, but your reviews on your ecstasy and your reviews everywhere else even for me and now I'll
Give a testimony your tarot reading is correct a thousand percent
I will vouch for you my wife can vouch for you a lot of people all your supporters about for you a lot of your stuff
He said
I didn't regret it. I've done great readings in the past few days
But that's like actually been able to do finally readings for people because I finally like
Okay, so okay. Well, here's our G
Here comes this one. Let's see how long I can
So it's like how long have I known you now about a year or so? No, you haven't known him for about a year
I saw you for the first time on that episode where you were doxing, beta, whatever that episode was
I guess a month ago, that's a month ago
You guys speak to psych and can you speak to concept? No, you cannot. No, you cannot
Let him talk let him talk you look like an absolute peckerhead just look at the shape of your face. You're new
Look at you turn your camera on
I thought you wanted to talk to psyche so you wanted to come up here see psyche
This is what he wanted to do. He wanted to come up here to talk to me
What's up with your face? What's up with your face that you have your face that you have what's up with your voice?
Why don't you?
You ever see you ever see?
Your voice
I think it's cancer. I
Think you have no voice. I think you're actually a female. I think you're actually a
Behind your face like this
You're wearing a bitch ass hat. Why do you do that, Argie? Why don't you quit?
Yeah, I've had this picture for a real quick stutter.
You suck at this you suck
Yeah, you do you do
Keep keep talking with psych you came up here
Anything else
That's what you are
See he wanted to come over here and just get on my neck that's what they wanted to do bro. It's what this
And you came up on panel why what did you come up?
And you follow me
Thank you for admitting that was your house today, by the way.
I thought it was in your B&B.
I thought it was a relative stuff.
It's just like a fucking book.
You lie and you lie and you lie.
And that means conveniently that you tell the truth.
You're a nobody, Argie. You're a nobody.
You admitted it was your house today.
You just hid it.
Hide with your fake little cacti's on your hand.
It's just like...
Those are not real cacti's.
Those are some fake-ass tattoos, fake-ass tattoos, like a mother fucker.
My body is covered in fake tattoos, you got me, you got me.
That's true, I can't even get as planter as this shit that's being talked about me.
That's what I that's why I care because I've known you to be a pretty intelligent guy since I've met you
However long it's been which was my original point the fact is if you don't see what this guy is doing then
Trying to convince somebody of something
That's what you did yes what you did
Sike he's not dumb enough to fall for your bullshit, Argie. You try to bullshit
He saw right through you she saw right through your bullshit
Why do you talk like be with some butt head? Why do you talk like a self-part character?
This rings are very fast.
Look at all the rings are very fast.
They are.
They have like this hole.
They have like that.
Why do you come like a fry?
You got like that.
I haven't talked to you anymore.
Why did you pick that voice?
Tell me, why did you pick that voice?
What voice did I pick?
Why did you pick Randall Graves voice?
You really think that I have an AI?
Why did you pick it?
Yeah, you did.
This is a voice changer.
Yes, you did.
1,000%.
You really are a fucking idiot.
Yeah, you're not Jeff Anderson.
Unless you are Jeff Anderson behind that.
Again, I'm trying to decide.
Are you Jeff Anderson?
Yes or no?
I'm trying to decide if you give a cancerous growth
on your nose.
Are you?
Yes, or no, yes or no. Are you Jeff Anderson? I got your Jeff Anderson somewhere in Canada.
Unless you are in Canada, are you in Canada in the wilderness somewhere? Maybe you're
You got me.
Yeah, you sound just like him.
And then the name you picked was the guy who got you.
Why did you pick that?
What are you talking about?
How many did you put that?
Why did you pick that?
Why did you pick it?
That's how he sells sea shorts by the sea shorts.
You can't even explain
Tell me that's not going coming out
You tough up, you look like a fucker head.
Yeah, you look like a fucker head.
You look like a little fucker head.
You give it a go.
Why do you talk like that, RG? Why?
I should be a voice actor just like you.
Is this what you call LinkedIn?
Is this what you think?
I honestly should.
You're a fucking idiot.
That's you. That's what you do, RG.
You're a voice actor.
Listen to this fucking idiot.
Keep going. Keep going.
You and your faggy rings?
You want me to go to Central or yes or no?
We actually have a discussion. Yes, 100% motorcycle. Yeah. It's the Harley gave to fat boy 2014
Let's see, I don't believe it. I didn't see no
Yeah
Think I'm stupid fuck you
Stupid motherfucker show it stupid. I'm showing shit. You can't afford a fucking you can't afford it. That's a fact a
2014 I can't afford a 2014. Okay, you can't afford nothing. You don't work
You guys thought I was an ice cream man, you guys are putting pieces together, you guys are putting pieces together that don't even fit, you guys thought I was an ice cream man, you can't even figure out what I need for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you don't know what the fuck I do for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you don't know what the fuck I do for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you don't know what the fuck I do for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you don't know what the fuck I do for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you don't know what the fuck I do for a living, you can't figure out what I need for a living, you don't know what the fuck I do for
he's known for two things he's known for lying on youtube and he's known for jack you're known for lying
dox named perlastin and v racist that's what you're known for rg lying and rassing dox and vina
racist that's exactly what you're doing that's exactly what the fuck he was thousand percent
that you don't have a house to
name a person that isn't a minority on your list, name a person that isn't a minority. You can't
because every person is all a minority. You have a lot of white art Caucasians.
That's exactly who you are. Yes, yes, 1000%.
Thousand percent you know me. Don't stop bro. Stop cap. I don't know you
Sorry
Yeah, Janet's white. She's not a black person. She's not a minority. Yeah, she is. He actually is again. It is a thousand percent a minority. Yeah, black. Yeah, she has black. Blacks don't claim her. I've talked to many of black people and not one of them have claimed Janet. Not one.
Who have you talked to? I doubt the Mexicans claim you either, to be honest. I haven't. By the way, in Mexico, you don't know any Mexicans. You don't know any Mexicans. They're no Mexicans.
You don't know mexicans in canada they would then we don't exist over there. We don't go in the cold
We don't fuck with that cold. Canada for us. Or are you talking about that cold weather? We don't fuck with that cold weather
We're talking about
We don't get there you go. There you go. That's what I mean. Slip it
You can't slip it
In chances we do not claim janet. She's not black
Absolutely, not black. She's absolutely not beautiful either. I don't know where the fuck she gets that from
Janet so badly tell me why do you go after Janice about it is because you want
Janet like a motherfucker who harassed Jimmy you harass me you harass a lot of fucking people
Only buddy who's cool with Jimmy you harassed. That's what you do
He knows what a fag J dog is
Nobody even knows who you're talking about, you fucking stupid fuck-
You were talking to Mason, how do you get Robin Tugs, dude?
Yeah, I was trying to tell him how to get Robin Tugs.
You were talking to Mason, not another disabled man.
How do you get Robin Tugs?
What do you do?
You harass women.
How do you present what you do?
You harass women, Argie, that's exactly what you do.
You harass Janice, and then you go harass Groovy Jimmy.
You harass the journey supporters.
You harass anyone that was with you without listening to you.
Why do you harass people?
Are you that pathetic?
you have nothing you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have you have
Fucking idiot, look at this guy, sounds like that, why do you sound like that?
Look at this guy, why do you talk like that, you sound like a fucking idiot.
Why?
That nose is like, why?
You got the sun in your nose.
Why do you talk like that?
Dude, that's cancer.
I'm telling you.
I've got a cancer, I've got a cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I've got cancer, I
I am the radiation that's going to destroy you, I am the radiation that's going to destroy you, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I touch kids, I
And everybody's children everybody's seen it we all know it our game
We all seen it so you can't line up. Don't back out
So you got so you Docs
Mentally handicapped
Handicapped person did you doc yes or no you just admitted to it you just admitted to it, so you harass mentally challenged
People yes, what you do
Five years old just admitted it. Yes, you just admitted it. Why three cards on the Internet
That includes you with why I'm not a recharge. You can't fuck with me. I don't know. You cannot
can't do that. I'm proving it since you've been up here. You don't fuck with me. You follow me.
I don't follow you. Don't forget that. Don't forget that. That's true. You follow me. I don't
follow you. I don't follow you, bitch. Remember that. J-Doc.
When this is over, I want you to go back and listen to it honest to God when that does over
I want you to go back and listen to it honest to God
I want you to go ahead and listen to what your voice sounds like honest to God
Why don't you do that?
Without the voice changer. Are you are you listening to this evening?
Yeah, so check it out. Um
I kind of been like sneaking around like I haven't really been in the chats much, but I've been around like listening and watching and
Jay dog, I heard you like I came up here last week and I wanted to talk to psyche about some shit that like I
Haven't been wanting to talk to him about and you were up here, and you were just going on and on about our G our G and
Follow just telling you like a retardist
I got one word in I got one sentence in and I asked I asked psyche
I said hey psyche like you know like how do you feel about Scorpios and Scorpios whatever and he was like oh and then he told me well
Then you cut him off completely and start talking about it again. Well, then anyways
It's not cooking Jnog
Shut up so that we can hear our Hebrew
And you're fucking going
Let me tell you what happened
Let him talk RG let him talk let him finish and like the whole looks thing
I don't care about looks, but you do look like a garden gnome. I'm just saying that part
Hebrew the only one who looks like a fucking freak is you if you take that hat off. You have patches on your head
And you're by the way
There you go there you go your Hebrew how old are you Hebrew?
Oh, they're like
I said I haven't had time to shave it yet usually usually I pick it with a razor
I haven't had time to do it. That's why it looks like that because it's growing out. Yeah, I'm going bald
I don't know man. Don't let that you don't come up here showing that shit off. Don't pull out. Oh, why would you auto?
I was just mad because it was like I wanted to have like a panel here and talk to psyche and you ruin that and then I
How can I ruin it at Jimmy's how can I ruin it at Jimmy's it was me and you and then and then Janet popped up
But like it was me and you in the beginning and you were talking about the same shit the same shit here same shit there
Yes, I have to do it.
I'm connected.
And the reason I'm talking about these guys right here next to me is that RG is right
here.
That's why I'm talking about it again, because RG is here.
There it is.
The clip that he got, the two clips, and now he's trying to get more and more clips.
Two clips, by the way.
Two clips.
He's counting them.
No, I'm not counting anything.
You're counting them.
Shit.
I only know one.
You're up here on your mind. I was up here talking to me
You came up here
I came up here following you
You followed me
You have no idea how other people see you
You tried to lie to Psyche
You've been up here for a year
You ain't even known Psyche for no year
I asked him because I didn't know
I barely pitched some months
The only reason he knew of you is because you doxxed Beto.
That's how he knew of you.
You doxxed Beto, you don't fucker.
And you're a pure child of a bitch,
somebody that you're good at.
They like you very much.
You are no good son of a bitch.
That's all you are.
He just thinks I'm a nice guy.
So there you go, J-Dog.
I've heard you doc's children
That's what people said
You see doc's little kids at your middle
Can they show proof of what children I've docked?
Nobody
You were there when you said doc's little kids
You know what I mean?
That was a question, not a fucking statement, dipshit
Oh, so he absolutely did
You were coming up here, first of all
How long have you been around Hebrew?
How long have you been around?
You have
Seven years by the way, you're not really good at it for seven years
You suck at this dude.
That's cucking the conkent.
Cucking the conkent by the way.
And you wanna talk about four wheels.
You're on a final that's called.
You wanna talk about four wheels.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's all you are G a stupid fuck trying to manipulate people into thinking that you're something, but you're not your piece of shit
You're scum. So you are just like this. Why what what picture is that that a I picture you have up there Hebrew?
No, that's me in my park uniform
Your park uniform. Yeah, I work in the store. I really think that's the answer on your nose, J dog
Parking anyways, can I say something?
So you're on a panel do you know what his channel is called like you know what you know, it is like he's channel is called
J-Dog J-Dog J-Dog
Asking about like Scorpios if that's what he's into like reading reading taros
Because there's a time and place for it and you stay up
Something else you stupid fuck and you want to come up
What was on Jimmy okay, we won't talk about psyches forget psyches
What were you talking about on Jimmy's that I that you were pissed at that I interrupt getting we're talking about RG
What was it on John is up there when he got porn bombed and then he had to shut it down. Remember that we were up there
You were up there, too
I've been up there a couple of times. I don't remember. I'm up there so many times like it's hard for me to remember
That's how I'm asking you for like a recollection
And I was, I was just like, I couldn't even say, Jimmy brought me up and I usually just like, hey, what's up Jimmy was gone.
I couldn't even say what's up to Jimmy because you were just like, I don't want to be rooted in a rugby, but you were going off.
And I was like, what the fuck, like, before I waited, I waited and then like 15 minutes went by and then Jimmy got porn bombed and that was it.
So I just left as a fuck it. I'm not going to stay here and waste my time.
This was just the other day. Yeah, I saw that too
So you were stalking Jimmy's that's what you were doing are you right? So you were stalking
Do that, why do you stalk another man? That's very very weird to stalk another man
I think though I would really think so I agree everybody would agree with me on that
You stalk Groovy Jimmy. Why do you do that, Argie?
Well, anyway, Hebrew, I'm sorry if I interrupted you.
I'm sorry if I cut you off.
I didn't mean any disrespect to you.
My bad.
like that bro i'm just saying like hey i don't mean any gifts on your nose you
legitimately have a cancerous growth on your nose it's the only thing that's
cancerous you are community community that's all you are your cancer
can actually be legit with you that's all you are
repeating what i say is actually cooking you actually think that
You think that you actually think that you actually think that
Like the best you could do
Why can't you stop talking about my boy Jimmy
Why can't you
So irrelevant
Why do you talk about the black dragon sir, but you have such an obsession with Tony the black dragon don't you I do
That is your stop talking about him next week. He never fucking jerked off for me at VC
Everybody knows
Yeah, yeah, you're fucking lying
You shit you're a liar
I'm sure somebody can set up your fucking proof, Doc Sucker.
Where's that, where's that fucker, Art Vanderleck?
Everybody knows it.
And that way he could kill that clip.
I'm sure somebody knows this, because you know it's true.
I'm not mad.
I'm trying to say, you and Tommy asked you about it today.
Wait, you and Tommy asked you about it today.
You were watching again today, too.
Why is that a surprise?
Fucking fucking piece of shit.
You're a stalker.
A guy who's fucking stalks another man. Wow
Tell me why do you stop
Man
He got six hundred bucks out of it.
You know the other day, is that make some of the bucks?
Is that for your stalker?
One hundred bucks out of you.
You're such an idiot.
How did you feel that you paid him six hundred bucks?
And now that he won't even allow you to come to where they have nothing else, how does that feel, I don't think they have absolutely nothing else.
It feels so good that you're still talking about dogfucking, right?
You're still talking about dogfucking. You're a simple-minded idiot, sir.
You are in love with another man. You are in love with another man. Yes, and it hurts you that he don't accept you.
Because Jimmy's not gay.
Jimmy's not gay.
We're gonna run with that narrative.
Just like Marty ran with the fact that he was in love with Syrax.
I'm gonna be in love with Jimmy now.
Okay, we can play it that way. That's fine.
I'm gonna tie Jimmy up and I'm gonna make him happy.
Why do you stop?
Let's run with that narrative.
I'm gonna tie him up and I'm gonna make sweet, sweet love to his African hyena.
Happy J doggies. Oh, you want to hear you fucking weirdo? You're sick. It's okay to be gay. So you know he's got it
You're sick. You want to rape groupie Jimmy? You're sick. Yes. Yes, I do
He's gonna die with me inside him he's gonna die with me inside him
Bro, see that's what he likes to do. This is he crashed out. He crashed out. This is what he ate while Hebrew. I'm sorry, man
No, just respect. I
Didn't mean to cut you off won't happen again. All right, my bad
You're me Jimmy's gonna die
Oh you got rid of J-Dog. I hope he goes and gets a cancer looked at out of his nose. What do you think?
you think Rudy? What do you think Rudy? What do you think? What's going on? Everyone's
Whoo
Okay, do you want to talk about Scorpios or no
Hello
Don't want to talk go away she's
Okay, I could tell you about Scorpius hold on a second
Just give me a minute
Whole video about it
Hmm. Oh my gosh, sorry guys
I am so sorry. I'm so sorry. Just give me a minute.
Just give me one minute, please. Give me one minute.
Please stand by.
She laughs and riddles, she whispers in flames
Plays hide and seek with the shadows and names
A lover, a trickster, a sorceress too
If you look in her eyes, she'll see straight
and score, be okay, so fly
She turns every argument
Excuse me fanny packs are for summer camp
Okay, god we got 35 bitches, okay
Thank you, Lillith
Oh, come on up whoever wants to come up
I'm on up.
What? Now you're ready to talk?
Hello?
Okay, Charlie Brown.
Kick it. Go away. Talk or leave.
Okay, leave.
Tracy
Oh, who is it? Oh, hold on
Ah
What's up, hello, what are you doing? It's what's up?
Hey, how are you doing? Oh, there we go. I'm hey
How are you today?
I got paid today.
So I got some weight-o's and a couple of tall boys.
Nice.
I got a copy.
I can get free copy until 1.30 today.
What time is it?
No way.
Oh, an hour late.
Yeah, they have like Cross the Street.
They open at Einstein Bagels.
They have unlimited coffee all day.
I can go through the refill and stuff.
Do you know, remember the Rat Pack?
Like Sammy Davis Jr.?
Yeah.
Yeah. Danny Thomas just died.
Well, God bless Danny Thomas.
Was he the last of the rats?
Well, he was like a sidekick in
the rat pack. But he was in the
same era as the rat pack.
It's good to see you.
Now I think you're all dead from
that era. Danny Thomas was in
You know
He was in he was in a lot of Danny Thomas was in sitcom. He did television. He did
Gas appearances I would say Danny Thomas was on the Johnny Castle show
Yeah
Well, he died when I see him, you know, how's your doggy doing?
Oh
Your little guardian fucking team was it it's like having a Doverman pension that weighs nine and a half
Well, it looks like he's having a good life
He's become a state of the city boy. He's a loon doctor now
Damn that crow is pissed off
Well, I don't know if you've been keeping track of what's going on, you know, it's been kind of crazy
I don't know, you know, I see I watched you this morning and it's the same old bullshit
Well, yeah, but it's about to be over because I just found out some new information that kind of like enlighten me a little bit
Today it was today today is what is today mark the state on the calendar. This is called 9 30
Yep, September 30th. 30 days past September. So it's the last day of the month. Tomorrow is 10-1. Today is 9-3. 93
93 million miles away from the Sun by the way
Yep
And uh, yeah, I don't know. It's like I mean today. I just figured out Alex doesn't make a good mod
So I think I'm a little bit slow
No, no, no, no Alexander McQueen not for on her
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not Alexandra Alexander McQueen. Oh
the cop. Yeah
Why did you give him? I
Don't know
No, he didn't but you know what?
Alexander today's decided to start his own stream yard and so he kept tagging me. Oh come to my
You know what you know what his stream was?
It was just a stream yard backdrop. No talking no video. Just the pure ocean buttons
Just pushing buttons
But then he said all he wanted to do was kick people off
He was just waiting for people to come up so we could be good. He blocked them and stuff
And wouldn't that be a piece of can you imagine people's seeing how long they'd last?
Alright, how long can you last
on the fucking on Alexander's
fucking stream? No, not I mean,
all he wants to do is keep
people. He didn't want to talk
or anything. That would be the
game of it. Do you understand
the concept where he's coming
from? How? He's insane.
He's insane. Okay, Hebrew
Hammers, but you know Hebrew
Yes. I've known Hebrew Hamas for years. Oh, but five years.
I was like, I'm like, oh my god, it's Tracy. I haven't talked to him.
I know I love you too. How are you?
Yeah, we were, we got close. Tracy's cool as fuck.
How's your mom?
She's not doing well. Okay. All right. I don't want to get in there. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She's kicking. That's how are you?
How are you? Ah, it's a beautiful day in New England. It's like this is what New England's all about
Yeah, you know and I got paid today so the rents paid
My fucking weedle stores paid off. That was five hundred fifty dollars. I spoke some hellish as we did you month
Sounds like it. Oh Jesus Christ
And how's he doing?
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh,
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
Now we're saying Mike. Oh
Shelling there goes my tablet. Mike. He's doing good. He's on he's not used to a chain
Yeah, he's a city dog
Yeah
Yeah, and and he had sex with my fucking stuffed animal in that big tiger. Oh
I think it's all wet. We've got a sex toy
Let's get a care bear
Yeah, like Monicles I like these like Monicles because they're only broken. It's you body care, but
Yeah, get him again that care bearing. I'll get it all wet and stuff
What was your man like cabbage patch? Oh
The drawing my kid was like Xavier three or four years old
and fucking they got sent to my uncles right because he was part of the
Legion or something like that were about to take it and he didn't recognize the
name and back then it was Tracy King had to bend my real name you know but
anyways so my kid didn't fucking get that and then it turned out that my son
was queer I bet he would have loved that doll as a little kid
you know what I mean
I mean, I would have bought
I mean, it's
I knew someone's up though.
Well, now they have dolls for
everybody, you know, they have.
Oh my god, when G.I. Joe came
out, my stepfather had a shit
fit.
Yeah, it was kind of hot. Yeah.
the guns and shit. Oh, yeah.
and it started coming out with
accessories. Then my stepfather
said my brother could have it.
Yeah, G.I. Joe was very
controversial. G.I. Joe. Oh,
really? I'm a hero. What
happened with Jay Dog? They
or he kept saying, discussing things about grape and stuff, you know, grape soda and I feel like this was just a Christ people.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, it gets too painful.
You're back in her day. Show the photo.
Oh yeah, you're saying, she needs to go in her safe to get that out, right? They're gonna save you.
I was just reading the photo.
I remember those photos. You're a hot mama.
Who?
Oh, yeah, I showed you your book. Yeah. I remember. I showed you the picture book from when I was like 20. I remember. I've never been the same. That's when I stole the flag and Papa said I couldn't have my American flag until he was dead, over my dead body.
Look, I don't know if you know. Do you know who auto is? OTTO is Tracy? Have you seen auto? I've seen that name before.
with Flirty Diamonds. He was up with Flirty Diamond. Flirty Diamond. Yeah, you do?
That's fucking whore on the damn street. Flirty Diamond was on. He was a straight guy.
Now he's turned gay, but then he started squirting lotion and rubbing it on his, and then I turned
straight.
And so, it all worked out for
everybody, right?
Well, actually-
Happy ending!
Hey, at least you guarantee a
happy ending.
Now I'm just like, I think I'm
just swerved off of sex for good.
I just like, you know.
I'm done.
Swerved hog!
that guy
Fucking insane
Oh my god, what does follow me around to this guy's panel and then started talking shit about me war dog
And I'm not a big fan. No, not a big all that guy. Oh my god
That guy is fucking
And he's got his mic down so well, you can't understand what he's saying
I like his, like, alien cat motif a little bit, but not really into him.
That's what you get when you pickle a brain in his brain, his fucking pickle.
A what brain?
the
It's three hundred dollars for an ounce and that ounce lasted me three days. We call those burnouts. That's what it is
That's what I was thinking about. Oh my god. No
That weekend I went to Maine in this
He's a nobody he's clicking fucking buttons again. Sorry
I know streaming I just put out a bunch of new buttons. I was looking but they want 35 hours a month
Well, yeah, I oh here comes me. Do you amazed then Tracy?
who?
meet Mason
Mason the drummer psyche. Yeah psyche. What's up? What's going on?
Pretty good man, what's up with you?
Thank you. I'm just chilling, but what do you want?
Well, so everything's like, okay
As well as they could be expected, right?
I heard something about
So I got hurt something earlier, man
Or something here something that happened something happened in here
What was it people that were um?
I think it was about some kind of drama or something like that right people are going on about drama or something
Oh, I know. Oh, baby. Look at it. We see Lenore Lenore. Come here
Oh, yeah
This is my good little girl
My baby looks like mine. Well, mine's got no tail. It's got like that. This is my baby
You guys don't see my baby. He's right here. Oh, let's see psyche. Yes. Yes, Mason
So where's all your cats? You have all your cats, would you right now Rudy and Lenore's here and tricks is probably around and so is
Lola she's around
Dog that's a beautiful dog. He's a short-haired pointer German pointer
I don't fuck it's my dog right there now, and point is, I just love a dog.
He's a bird dog.
Bird dog.
He's a bird dog, ain't you baby?
He is.
Get that bird.
The Psyche.
Yes, Mason.
Is everything alright?
Did you see the videos, did you see the videos I showed you?
Psyche, like the different videos I sent you.
The drag queen that plays video games?
No, I'm talking about some new ones that I sent you I got you some new ones in your G-Belt
Which one?
You have to check it out when you get a chance. I will
This is see if you like them psyche, they should be good videos
Before I can go look let me see. Oh, my tablet's charging up. Can you tell me what it is for a quick?
What is that cats? It's like videos. It's like videos from YouTube and stuff like that
So I can stuff I found on YouTube
It's a wild name to come up with for a cat.
Would you know somebody that was a Lenore?
Yeah, well, no, she's named after, like, you know, Lenores, like...
like black the black. It's like
black cat. I think it had to
be there's in uh the the
we're like ****ing me ****
because I didn't like when
I mean, yeah, we're all here
we're all here. Go ahead and
You're a bad little winner, Gino.
You're a black guy on me.
Glenn and Gary.
Saki, you like video games, right?
Yeah.
Is it that drag queen again playing video games?
Saki, what other video games do you like?
Because I have different video games I showed you,
like on your Gmail.
I have second life.
You like second life?
Second life.
I've played that before. That's like a like a I have a VR headset and it's like having a second life
I have yachts motorcycles nice how
Living Marina
Yeah, well on Grand Theft Auto I once had a no I can't play
I don't I haven't played video games in a while mate Mason. I'm a little bit too busy for video games
I wish yeah, you've kind of moved up in the world my new video game is called YouTube
Streaming
Yes, sir, I really like that song that taxi take a text taxi to
And I really did I really enjoyed it. I played it. Oh you did
I adapted that from an Elisa Giordano song called Dark Side of the City.
I know he asked you and that's what you told me and I tried to find that song but I couldn't
and I found it and then I played it and it didn't really, I don't know, I like your version a lot.
Yeah, you'll know. Well, I love her version too, but yeah, I just kind of changed the
You know music. It was cool. Thank you very much. Thank you very much
I'm gonna take a taxi to the troll side of the city
To tell your mommy a poppy will meet me who writes is AI program out for new
No, I write it and then you come up with a word
Yeah, but I was an easy one because I just had to like kind of just tweak the lyrics a little bit
No fucking way. Yeah, but I write the song and then you got one hell of a brain
Thank you
and uh
And then you can put it to any kind of like style of music and I usually mix up a few styles
Like I just like to like experiment and then I can usually
And
Why you because people you know, I've been just getting so many insults that I
Yes, yes Mason
So why does your camera keep
I miss having coffee with Stella. I was just thinking about this. What's wrong, Sasaki? What's wrong with your camera, man?
What's wrong with it? It's actually just, you know, trying to like move along with me, which is like erratic a little bit.
I fucking loved that run. Me too. Uh-oh. Hey, okay. I gave her a thousand dollars, great guy.
I was just thinking about, just thinking about. I do. I miss her every morning, about seven o'clock in the morning, six o'clock in the morning.
You know
Hey Psyche
Yes, Mason
Did Natalie ever come back to talk to you again or she like has it come back?
I haven't seen her today. I haven't seen her today. I just saw her last night and hopefully she
Comes in hangs out soon. Natalie's awesome. Well, that's what he's got more here on the side of the panel
Have you heard of it? Have you heard the song, Tracy?
No, I didn't. I played it.
Did you play it this morning?
No, I didn't. I haven't played it yet.
Hey, if you don't, I'll play it.
No, I'm just saying, did you play it this morning?
I like it a lot, actually.
You like it? Okay, let me see that.
I was just...
Troll side. Oh, it's right. It's one of my it is it just turned out really good, but let me see
Second versus killer. I thought AI was
Well, it means it does them I put the lyrics into this music
Here it is, okay, hold on a second here you go
This is a psyche. Yes one second Mason. We're gonna play the video real quick one second. Okay, okay?
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna turn the volume up. Okay, here we go.
I feel like I've been locked out
Spent my soul in a way I shouldn't have thought of
A part of my brain was fried
i thought that i could win but the chat just sighed won't you punish me they said i wasn't reasonable
nothing was debatable with me i tried to flood and pull one over all the mods who fed me but what
Take a taxi to the troll side of the live stream
Don't tell your ma team, your admin will need me
On the corner with emojis
Didn't you know that he was lonely?
Got me feeling muted
I'm about to get booted
Drama's over-computed
Asking me to give it a rest
do you see the yes I'm gonna take a taxi to the troll side of the
Is there different versions?
Cause that sounds like...
Hey, we've been hit.
This is the best one ever.
I actually like it.
Because you promised me a lot, you gave me less
You wanted my cloud, you needed my mess
Oh, you said that you don't-
who doesn't.
The version I'm fucking cool.
It's a little bit different.
Yeah, those two versions of it, yeah.
Yeah, the other one.
But they're both good, but yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah, I like it.
I like this one.
I haven't heard the other one.
But is it on your stream?
On your page?
It's all, yeah.
It's in my videos.
Yeah, it's on regular videos.
Okay, so all I gotta do is go to your channel.
Yep.
I have a few.
I have probably have it on my uh, what's it called mix cloud or something like that. I'll pin my mix cloud to um
It has all my circuit so I can hear them both
Yeah, I totally stole it and I played it on my channel
Anyone has permission to use any of my stuff like all my
Summer here. Hey, what's up summer?
What's up? What's up everybody?
Hey girly, what's up?
I'm having fun and got paid to do the rents paid.
And we don't mean that.
What's up, man?
Hey, Sikey.
Yes, nice to meet you.
Well, don't listen when CB tells you something.
Sikey, when CB tells you something,
don't listen to him.
He's lying and stuff like that.
How do you know?
I don't know.
What do you say?
Sikey, what?
But he said something that's not true psyche. He was making up stuff about me so I can don't listen to him though
Okay, I won't I'm gonna look for his comment. Oh, he's saying you're may send the news flash
He's why you got to have a Google account and be on YouTube
That's not true
Okay, I know he's like he's not true at all. I know it's like it's not true at all
Ignore him. Ignore him. He's just like Joker
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, Joker's trouble. Oh, the
last night we did a raid on
Joker's stream. It was really
cool. Like, did you? I was
trouble. He has too much fun.
His hair was like, he's in an
afro now. I was pretty sure.
He's fine. Joker is fine. He's
fine. But, um, what's it? You
know, dude was forcing himself
out of me. What's that noise?
I think it might have been me.
I'm not playing anything.
Okay.
I think it might have been me.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was muted.
I didn't do anything like yeah, I was just you're fine mason mason don't let people bother you. Okay, just
No, no, thank you. I'm saying I didn't have anything playing in the background though
That wasn't
It was me for sure because I my headset has a button on it to mute
You on the stream and I forgot that I hit the button
you know I have over 400 of these check it out let me see some like the couple. Oh my
gimp he's a gimp. Oh yeah. Oh my god. I have like 400. That's pretty cool. Tons of them
yeah. I love the games. I like the first one. So cute. He was in uniform. Okay then.
So I can see it's like God he wants to come up or something like that
He's showing like the street yard link. Does he need the link? I'll put the link up again. Hold on. Here you go
Yeah, cuz the one you got in your
I think I think God he wants to come up psyche. Yeah, I'll link from thank you sticky mason. Yeah, that's me
I'm not my park ranger uniform. Yeah, or I'm gonna see you in your park grader uniform and
Give the shorts
Um, yeah, well not anymore. I don't have any of it anymore. That was that was years ago
Are you married? I'm not no, I'm not married and I have a lot of issues like you wouldn't want to you wouldn't want to date me
Hmm. I have a lot of issues too. So I think we'd be okay. Yeah, but it's
Yeah
You're just very cute. Thank you. I appreciate that. Thank you very much
Him is a good guy though. It's nice of you to say that. Yeah, look
Yes, yes summer
So I'm on my way, you know how I go out on Wednesday nights
I'm on my way to go to go collaborate with the lady that does our hot mills and see if I can get another
Another thing of hot mills for two more days. So I can go out
Is your average tonight or tomorrow or is it well average is tomorrow night
But that way I can do it more than just Wednesday night
I go out more than just Wednesday night, but I don't have hot mills
Oh, you know on those days because I don't have the access to them
But this lady, she has a big organization.
She has like a big, you know, like restaurant style,
a restaurant, her kitchen, and she cooks all these like hundreds and hundreds of hot meals
for different outreach groups that go out, her and her team do.
And so I talked with her the other day and she was like, come in,
I want to give you another day so you can have more food.
That's awesome. We did art out of it. Everyone check out Hot Mess Summer. She has amazing outreach work. She helps a lot of people. Yeah, she does. She helps a lot of people. She helps a lot of people. She helps a lot of people. She helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot of people. Yeah, she helps a lot
That's those the summer get free mills though like the mill she gets there free like you don't have to pay anything to get
I don't charge people. I give them food. I give them clothes. I give them flashlights. I give them 10 sleeping bags
I don't charge them for any of that. That's one thing
To give back like
What they do have get stolen on them quite frequently putting your link in because
I really want to
And you can't do it now
You can't do it now
So that's summer's link
That's the reason why I go to work so I can do the things that I do so I don't have to charge people and people donate to me, too
So I can't where did you go?
I'm right here. I'm right here. I'm just putting the link at summer. There's summer. I'll see you on camera right now
It's like
So I can't I see so I get one off camera for a while
Yeah, it's okay
I've needed it and it's very appreciated if he goes off camera mates and it's okay. He'll be right back
Yeah, I was a heroin addict for like 18 years and then I went to prison and got clean and when I got out
That was one thing I did was to give back was I served meals out of a an old UPS truck is what used
Well, and it was a really rewarding and like it gave me like a peace of mind for a little while
I got to know a lot of cool people, but
Psycho, weren't you trying to do something? That's why you weren't on camera for a while. I'm no, I'm just right here
I was posting on Lake Mason. I'm cool. I'm right here
So and Mason I played the drums for like three years
the drummer
I'm a drummer too. All right. I'm about to pull up to my beat. So wish me luck. I'll talk to you guys soon.
That's summer. I love you. Good work, okay? I appreciate it.
I'm really so glad you came to see me.
Thank you. The thing I was trying to figure out is like...
So I think I was trying to figure out it's like he left for a while and I didn't see you like I thought I didn't know what happened
You know I'm saying I like I thought you're gone
Sneaking around all over the house. He's a tricky one. I'm trickster. I'm a little trickster. He's like a little ghost
Look at my beard's turning all gray. I'm see this is all from YouTube
Notice I have like a couple little grays in my beard the other day. I was like what the hell
I don't know. I showed you the I showed you one side of the specific. You can see the other side. Hold on. Oh
Remember I showed you my tattoo. Yeah, I saw your tattoo, but I didn't
Okay, now my camera's died. Oh my gosh. I just like wonked out the camera. Fuck. Okay, hold on
I don't know. I don't know if you've ever seen him
If you ever see this fucking maintenance guy
Where is my oh, shit. What did I do? Oh, is he okay?
Trace
Tracy yeah, oh shit. Is you all right? Oh
Tracy dropped off probably have to take care of it. Yeah, let's see if I can get my camera back on psyche. Yes, sir
that
Okay, did it work? Okay. Hold on. I got it. I got it.
The camera's all fucked.
Not good. Not good, guys.
Might have to take a couple days off to get my camera fixed.
Really? Use your phone.
It's not.
Yes.
Have you tried so I ever need protection from J dog
Yeah, why was J dog gonna do you we could protect yourself
Sike your psyche doesn't make sense like what why would I need protection from a J dog? What did J dog ever do to me?
I don't think psyche said that
That he was a protection
No
Fuck it
You easily trigger don't let them trigger
Don't let them what we said don't trigger you
I'm not trying to let them get to me. Yeah, don't let me you're better than that
Hey, what's up, Brian? I hope you're doing well. Nice to see you, Brian.
You got one of those electric rollers, those are cool.
Yeah, me and fucking Stella used to roll together.
She's the one who taught me how to get the one in there. The same one she got.
So you're a drummer too, man? Is that what she told me?
Yeah, yeah, like I've been playing since I was about nine years old
What is your name though, man?
My name is Robert Hebrew hammer. You can call me Robert Robert. What's up?
What's up, man?
So yeah, I've been playing drums you say call you Hebrew right not Robert. Yeah, Hebrew is good. Yeah
People I've been playing drums since I was like 10 or 11 years old
I've been playing for like 20 years or so since I've been playing
Really? I've been playing 23 years, and I just picked up the mandolin like four years ago. I just bought a drum set
Did you really? I bought an electric one, bro. Oh electric. I got an electric
Nice
Do you know what do you know what brand it is?
No, it's upstairs. Okay. You're good. No worries. This is good boy. Yeah
Hey fucking boy, I can't wait to get a house. So I it's got headphones. So you
Yeah, they can't
Yeah, I used to when I used to have an electric just a pad a single pad
I used to play snare on it. So I'd plug my headphones into it and play snares phone
Um, I can't play like covers on the drums like songs used to but you played it on the drums like that you hear
When I first started playing the drums
I went to a place called weather's music and I had a drum teacher for three years and you taught me how to play like I
Learned how to play like the whole Tom Petty and Heartbreakers album. Oh, yeah, I play a lot of tool enema
Yeah, I can play a lot of covers. Yeah, blink when you a lot of blink a lot of the tool
Hey, bro, can you play any disturb like covers on the drums like or any like other bands like that?
You know about here's the issue
I went to I had a I had an apartment and my drum so I was in there
Well, I went to prison and all my stuff went into a storage unit and then
My storage unit got taken like like I couldn't pay it so they auctioned everything off so I lost my drum set
So I haven't really been playing anything newer like it's been six years since I've played and you've been busy busy
I haven't been able to really
play. I mean, I have a man to
win. I pluck on my man. You've
got a man to win. Yeah, just
you know, he's raised in blue
grass. That's the one instrument
he don't have. He's man. I was
going to say the other side of
it. Look. Yeah, let me see
that. Turn it kind of. Oh,
there you go. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Thank you. That's what is it? There's some it's called
Pentacle of the Sun
It's got many what you what you for
It's well, these are like they're basically protection
Yeah, this is this tattoo is like my protection from demons like to keep demons and
away from me
Yeah, I'm gonna get my cross
psyche
pentagram
No, pentagram. Oh, it's against God
Yeah, yes Mason
a pentagram isn't where were you stuck at and see for a while. I had to go right
Mason, I had to go
Okay, so a pentagram is actually a moment of private
Yeah, the pentagram is like
When it's the right side up, it's like, you know the five elements
It's the five sides and so then it's like them
It's like almost a man inside of it
You can fit a man inside of it and then when it's on the side. It's like
the goat's head, right? And so, um, that's the, maybe, like, the...
What's died to me is, like, like, the American...
Saki, you know what Gotti said?
Okay, Mason, you should go into the chat and talk to Gotti, okay?
Saki, I wanted to tell you something, though.
No, tell me, tell me real quick.
Saki, I wanted you to know what Gotti said about me.
Okay, what did he say about you?
He said psych will protect you of get in bed with him. That's what he said about me. Come on. Come on. Come on
Averted pentagram. Yes, because that's the goat's head
On the right side, it's like a whole man, right? But on the left side, it's like the health man or like the whatever
Duality and then the singularity with the man the spirit on the top
and then with the goat, it's kind of like the
the side of the earth, right?
I got you.
Cool.
I invented really...
Damn, you can connect things all different ways
and mean all different things, huh?
Right.
You're interpreting the thing, I'm sure.
It's all an interpretation, I guess.
Yeah, yeah, I think stop, come on.
I always knew that the upside down one was the devil.
Well, yeah, but then it's like it depends on what you look at it because you can say like there's a pentagram, right?
Yeah, but then it's like it but then it's upside down second version, right?
All perspective
It's just like my flag
Well, Brian, it's like you can choose not to believe in them. That doesn't mean they're real or not
You know, it's like they can be considered parts of your mind, you know the demons that can be super parts of your brain
different
I don't believe in spiritual demons, but I believe in like my own demons like I don't want to release my demons to like
I don't want to you know
Natalie actually has talking about that Pandora encounters with that's a little she's like has sexual encounters or you know with who's uh
What another diamond is a little
No, she's actually she's a woman in um in England and she's really super interesting and she yeah
She has had astral
encounters with
Who she describes as Azazel and he has this red skin. Oh, yeah. Oh, she played
Thank you. I took like I'm contrapped Zozo
It's like Zozo. That's like Saturn, right? It's like, you know, it's like, I think it's like an attorney and give me Zozo. Yeah. Let me see. I can look it up.
All I know is when you use the board, like the Ouija board, you can call Zozo and like Zozo comes through the Ouija, they say.
It's like Oz. It's like Ozzy, the Wizard of Oz.
Yeah, and now elf ring bomb was actually what was he he was a like whatever madam
Blavatsky or a theosophist right and so the Wizard of Oz is a lot of theosophical
which is like philosophical it's like Sophie is wisdom and Theo is God so it's like the
wisdom of God yeah but the Grand Wizard from the clan come on you're talking about the clan
no i'm not talking about that i'm not talking like so i'm talking the Grand Wizard the one
who talks to the devil himself he first started in the school they was in there and they were
and he actually saw it. So,
that's a gateway. Mears are
blood. Eventually, he ended up
being the grand wizard of the
and now he's a Catholic. I'm
going to say that's a very
if I want to make fun of you,
Don't fucking accuse me of making fun of you Mason. If I was if I was making fun of you, you'd know it
Mason's a good type of Mason you're pretty good you're writing paragraphs and shit like yeah, yeah, he's fucking really studying hot
I'm back later. I'll f*****g create a whole f*****g profile for you. I'll make fun of you later. All right. Oh shit. All right. So, uh, later on.
Send me a link. Don't, don't make God mad. Okay, Mason. He's wrathful. You shouldn't do that. If some people you shouldn't f*****g with Mason.
You know, not unless you get the fucking ability to know how to do it
Get some coffee
Coffee I got a lot of stuff off my chest today, but now I feel how you did I feel I feel better
No, I don't feel better. I feel
What's this you feel like you got some shit off you just you needed to say I did I mean that that part feels better
But it's like I just don't know you gotta live with what you said
Well, I didn't say anything that bad. I didn't say no, but what the decisions you made you have to stick to
Right, I mean it's and I that's hard, but it's like it's hard accepting
And you because you're an ass kisser you want everybody to love you psyche earlier earlier when J-Dog was up here J-Dog said
Yeah, we were talking about something white like white and he was like making fun of me because I asked you about the Scorpio thing and I said
Do you understand what his name the name of his like should stay there channel wasn't like what he's into?
Maybe like shit for asking you
I'm sorry for that and it's like but I'm the I'm the expert
ability stick to what the channel is about
Right, but it's channel also like you know
In the drama community
No, no, no, I'm not bitching about any of it. I was just saying I thought it was funny that he was like
He's like why would you even ask something about Scorpio? And it's like well because you know like the guy
But you know all I know about Scorpio is don't piss them off because they are very well see I'm a Scorpio and I'm
That's October. It's going to be October-November, I think, right?
October-November story.
And I'm with the Scorpio, and then I'm like kind of like in love with another Scorpio.
So we're like, it's kind of weird how there's like just three Scorpios in a little game.
A lot of competition.
I would love to look more into your chart because there's probably a lot of interesting
things in your chart. Like, and you know, it's like, there's, because there's so much, I mean.
because there's the Scorpio Sun sign but there's also the Ascendant which is how you appear to people
and then there's also the Moon sign which is your emotional side and then there's all the
other planets on the chart too and so everyone's very very unique it's like a fingerprint right
it's like nobody has to exact same yeah every second and every day that all the planets and
stars align in a different way that's your signature your cosmic signature is what it'll
Very fucking worth it. I paid for somebody doing a birthday. I found out
Virgo Mercury Mercury
Virgo, so your Virgo son and then Mercury as well I'm Virgo
Worth it it's worth it to get the reading and they can
Then you can download it so you have it and I'll tell you what it's
If you want to like if anyone wants to pull up their chart
And there's astro.com and then just put it in your like information
And then you can get your chart and then I can you know
You can let me examine or astrologer or even like astro.com will have free reports you can look at
Well, don't you do that when it wouldn't they pay would they pay you the money you look at?
Well, yeah, but I do really cool things like I'll put it to mute
I'll make a song with it and I'll incorporate
Symbols into it. I'll make art with it
Can you make a song about me?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Really? It's gotta be a fucking bang up.
Fuck, it's like, you know the kind of music I like.
Yeah. Oh my gosh. You know, you're like...
Bargy Biker Music?
Like the, you like the, like the, like the Flingwood Matt kind of or like more, more hard rock?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
How much does that cost?
Well, um, let me see. I like, like, I think for, well, 25 I'll do like the uh,
No, I want the whole package, because I'm going to fucking incorporate it with the channel. It'll be there forever.
Yeah, okay. Oh my gosh. I've made really, really, like, really cool art. I used the Sabian symbols too, because everyone has, like, every...
Everybody has, like, you know, they're 360 degrees, so they're 360 Sabian symbols. They all have a specific symbol.
Ooh, I like that. And you can actually, like, take the symbols.
Put the symbols into a song and also into art and things like that. I don't want it as long as all your other songs are they too
No, no, no, it'll be totally unique to you. Totally. Okay, totally. Absolutely
All right, and um, and I'll also go into your calls though 25. Yeah 25 25 bucks. Yeah
And I'll have interesting information about like your most interesting placements, and I'll put a lot of other information
And it'll be a whole report. I've done one for spunky and she loved it
It'll be an intro song that I play while people are coming in and chat
I would love to I would love to that would be fucking kind of like that fucking DJ fucking electric it for you
And got you started with this shit. Yeah, she's a bitch. She was a big inspiration
That fucking broad smile this out. Yeah. Yeah
She got you into something fucking fun something you're learning about
But yeah, right me a fucking
kick-ass
fucking X
fucking
Intro song I'll pay you 25 bucks right shit. You got it. You got it. I get paid every two and a half weeks, so
Uh and another week and a half. It's on a Thursday. I fucking get paid. I'll fucking whichever app I don't do Venmold
I got PayPal and cash out
I'll do it for you like, you know, if you click just all the time in the world
Okay, well just send me your um info info on um your birth info on Instagram, you know, and then I'll get into your chart
You got a fire
You'll love it very unique cuz I'm not anybody I've never heard anybody else doing this kind of thing like
It'll be absolutely unique to you absolutely yeah, but we gotta have it fucking like
You know I you know me. Yeah, God. I'm gonna see what you began this shit
Look, I'm gonna ask you psyche. Have you heard of the book? It's called the book of birthdays and it's like a very expensive
It's like a secret language of birthdays a secret language of birthday. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I think that's what it is. Yeah
What did you do?
It'll tell you anything about your like the day you were born like like I might have read Tracy hers. Let me see
Yeah, I read it and it's totally true. Yeah, mine is too. I'm actually, you know, Alexandra and I have the same birthday, which is a different year, but we have the same birthday.
Well, were you born on the same day? Yeah. No, I mean, was because yours could have been a Wednesday and hers could have been Monday.
Well, so we're a couple of years off, so it was probably a different day, I think. Different day, like I was born on the same day.
I have a Wednesday. I was born on Wednesday, which is uh, well Tuesday is Mars. Wednesday is um
Odin's day, you know
Odin
Explains a lot
Stop and faster. Thank you third of November
11111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111
Um, January 7th like so one seven which is equals eight, but then it's like, you know, and then my
965 it was the first set of numbers. I have a fucking
Right there's so much you can learn from the numerology and the birth path and like
It's so important
That's when your stars and your planet alignments
And the stars align, you know, you know moon how the moon is when you're born with the moon phase, right?
I mean everything is so unique to you. You know each of us, but it does tell you can tell you so much about
Hey, Jamie. How are you? So we are on the phone
Does Jamie I did read a text today from somebody, you know, I read the text. It was a really shocking text
I read
Does it matter like um, does it matter like the time?
Well, yeah, your birth time too because it's like the it like during the day your moon can the moon can be an
Everything moves. Yeah, and so it's like it does matter. You usually want to get your birth time and stuff
Because that will is close. Yeah, as close as you can
And it should be if you want the time of birth go to the hospital
that you were born in
and get an original burst to get from them and it'll have the time that your ass entered the world
I'm pretty sure my mom knows because I was a big fat baby and she fucking hated being
14 hours fucking over 11 pounds and so I was 10 pound you were 14 pounds and you were 11 pounds
I was 10 pounds and I thought I was big 14
He was
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I wasn't 14 pounds
I was like 11 pound baby or something like that
I was an exact other perfect 10 10 exactly. That's crazy
Yeah, I was 22 inches long. Oh, wow
I do have a baby book somewhere. I think in my bedroom and it has like my hair
My hair was so blond that it was like white. I was in tow head
Sike I don't understand but uh, there's people that are like coming at me like in the chat
I know I know they ignore them, but that's what I've been doing
But I'm saying I've been talking just regular but uh, they did something where I can't even message anymore though psyche
in the chat they had these blocks maybe it's just take a time out they can just take a breather
because it's like I think you're getting upset about it and just like you know you can hang out
in the site smoke good job if you look in the chat if you look in the chat you can psyche how am I gonna
Sike, how am I gonna talk to people in the chat like you want me to do though if they actually time me out though?
I can't actually do a thing in the chat.
Hold on, let me check. Let me check out what happened. Hold on. Guys, don't hide Mason.
Wait for me, Mason!
Yeah, don't fuck with me. Come on, Mason's a good guy.
Sike, I thought I was your cool friend and stuff like that. I never did anything like that.
Did Mason get timed out or something? Let me see. Hold on. Oh yeah, hold on.
Gotti, come on. Hold on.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay
I know you don't. He said he did not. Okay. I don't know who did. I thought I said Gotti did something but Gotti, come on
Don't do it no more
Yeah, I think Gotti wants to talk to you up. It's like, you know, I think time didn't hide Mason. Okay. Did it was a Gotti?
So I guess I wanted to time me out though. I just want to know that though. Like I don't know who time me out
Gotti, was it you? I saw something about Gotti in there, but hey Mason you're untimed out. I untimed you
Yeah. You're fine. You can go talking with that.
So I keep I just wanted to just you know, say what I feel like I just wanted to say my opinions and stuff like that
Wasn't trying to do it like I wasn't trying to get in trouble or anything like that
I'm not trying to get trouble. I don't know what I can't pay attention to like the chat the chat completely right now
Time you are a mod and he's a mod you can you work it out between yourselves like man? I mean come on
You got it me so you can go adults. Oh
We all got you back go ahead you got this way
Dispected spam caller
Sike, you know like you know the whole time I've been with you like we've always got along so I mean
I don't know like it's just other people that there's
There's something off about them.
There's something that happens off about them.
Guys, please stop upsetting Mason, OK?
Just let him talk and be nice to him, OK?
He's ball's a job.
They're just trying to get you all riled up, Mason.
Just don't let him get to you.
Just chill.
Hug it out.
Hug it out like men, Mason.
Just hug it out.
Saki, they're just trying to get the best of me.
Saki, you're trying to see things get like the best of me
is what they're trying to do, I think.
Don't let them win.
Don't let them win, Alan.
Thank you.
There's my others.
There's my Scorpio.
I gave her I gave her your link though. She's in here now. Yes
See awesome
Yeah, leave Mason alone J-Doc said leave me so yeah, can someone look after
Just stop fucking with him guys fuck give him a break for a minute, so we don't have to listen to
Fuck man
You guys know exactly what you know. Thank you so much
Yeah
You know you're you're a good dude Mason and not maybe people don't understand that but not everyone but I think
ignore
You can do a lesson how to like you know kind of because there's gonna be trolls and there's gonna be mean people sometimes and it just helps you
They're gonna deal with them better. Okay psyche psyche even J dog was to psyche even J dog was telling somebody to leave me alone
He's like leave Mason alone. That's what he was telling time. I think his name was time or something like that
Yeah, with him with J dog. He's you know, he's a
J dog to help you out. Yeah
His J dog is a
Yeah, J dog
Jay dog, did you really get offended when I said you look like a garden gnome? I was like
I was just telling you how I felt like I fucking I
Don't know. That's what popped into my head the first time I saw you the ground when I saw you
So don't be offended by that. I look like a fucking
I look like fester from the atoms
I'll see how I look like
I
Looked like somebody not very flattering. I'll show you who I look like let me see
Well, okay, I got you J-Doc. I'm just psyche
I never had a problem with you and I never had a problem with J-Dob
But it's just other people they they got on like they got on me for nothing
Well, fuck
Mason look people say I look like this
What did you want me to know psyche told me something, but what did you want me to know?
I want you to see who I look like here. Look at this. Watch this. I look like this
Look who I look like
Look at this
No, you do
That looks you suck it. That's you. Is that supposed to be you psyche? That's too creepy
You do kind of look like him. Yeah
I'm waiting for the devil to psyche. Who are you trying to be like the Charlie in the
Chocolate factory or something like this anybody I was
Might they swap my face and they also leave a bell in there. Oh my gosh. Do you want to see something else? Oh
Hey, oh, it's a Tracy. Do you know I met Alexandra?
Yeah, she's this right here
watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch this, watch
I was just curious because like SDA just came out with a video called Ernie knows Mason
I was just curious if that's really up here than that pops up
I don't know who that is like who is the who's he talking about psyche? I've never heard of that
Ernie show yeah, I suck you doesn't ring a bell man. I don't know
And Brian, nobody needs to scroll back.
Nobody needs to scroll back and look at comments.
Just, we know what's going on.
Just fucking people just chill out.
Fucking leave the dude alone, just chill out and have, you know.
Yes, I can.
I'm just having a normal conversation.
So I just want to be like chilled on here too.
Yeah.
I know.
I know you do, dude.
You're good, man.
You're good, Mason.
Don't worry about it.
Like yeah, I was just talking about drums and stuff like that earlier because I played a drum psyche
So I'll let him know about the drums the guy named Hebrew. Yeah
We both play the drums, yeah, so like he plays the drums just like I played a drums, so we're both drummer. Yep
23 years I want Mason to get his drums drum set back or some set of drums. He sold his drums. Oh, yeah
I want my at least like a you know, at least a pink can with a drumsticks or something like I tell you what is a guy on YouTube
And he's outside of fucking Vegas. I know you're talking about
five
The glittery and he takes his foot and he picks up the place the symbol
Yeah, and he could play that he plays the symbols with his feet. Good. I know exactly who you're talking about
Yeah, he's one of my favorite drummers of all time. Oh my god
He's amazing and
He gets the crowd involved like how the crowd come up and hold symbols and shit
Um
He's out California or Vegas. I think it's Vegas
it's vexed
fuck it, that motherfucker is non-stop
his name, um, his name is Matthew Pretty
he R-E-T-Y, Matthew Pretty, and he fucking kills it
you guys, he's fucking unbelievable
he is off of a five gallon drum and sticking his foot up underneath
it depends on how much air you give that fucking, fuck it, it's what sound
Oh, well, like you can take lids. I know how to do it, too
Like you can take lids and fill them fill so much of them up with so much sand and
And then flip them over and it'll make different sounds and people play like you can play like an empty one
Which makes a very hollow sound and then they put they do these sand a lot, too. Um, yeah
I knew I once knew a guy that
Doing that shit, too, but he uh fucking cool. He died
If you ever get a chance to watch it, can I can I put this in the back?
Here check this out. This is him the guy you're talking about
This is the best one that he
That I've ever seen him do I
Don't know psyche will if it'll let me do this in his back shed or not. I think it will I don't have to be blue
Do I hear it?
psyche you're blue right you're the owner of the channel can you copy that link
that's in the private chat and throw it in the chat or not do you do that thank
you buddy and if anybody gets the opportunity to watch that video is
fucking amazing you can even fast forward and just check out seconds of it
it's amazing yeah I just fucking I brought it up and then I put it away for
watch after this yeah he's amazing yeah it hits the back chat
No, that guy's fucking yes, and he does it like every night
Dude, there's another guy. He has like a bunch of PVC pipes
And they're like bent in weird ways and he plays them with them flip-flops like his paddles are
Uh-huh, and he plays like techno and it's like
So fucking cool, he's really like
He's really good, yeah
Exactly. Hey, Bruce. I want to see you. Yeah
Have you heard of the band? Have you heard of the band on Lincoln Park?
Are you into them? Or do you listen to them?
No, I mean, I know a lot of people who are I have a lot of friends who are but that's just not me now
I never really got into Lincoln Park very much
Well, you like Hebrew if you had to find a band that you listen to
My favorite band I would have to say like my favorite bands are like tool a perfect circle
Um, yeah, I heard of the deftones. Yeah. Yeah, I know about the deftones. Yeah
You heard a song called move a shove it or something like that from the deftones
It's called like my own summer and it's called
Shoved it at they of course
Yeah, I know every deftones song by heart like I've followed them like religiously. I
Like the song they're a good man
Hey, we're they're a good band man
Maynard from tools. Yeah, no, they're very good. Yeah, they're really good. Yeah
They take a song called passenger riding the feature the guy from tool like in the song
Yeah, like right Maynard from tool sings it. Yeah, it's really good. It's one of my favorite song
I heard of it. I heard that song before
Yeah
Hey, psych, you're doing okay, man.
Okay, I'm just like a little messages right now.
I'm sorry.
He's good, he's great.
He's multitasking again.
What would you be saying?
Psych, I'm just checking on you psych
because I didn't know what was going on
if you just went quiet.
Yeah, I mean, I like, um, bleeding through, um, thrice, cinch, um, Metallica's all right.
I like a lot of canterra, and then I like oldies, like, real, real, real, real, I like
the highway men.
Shit site. My favorite band is a disturbed. That's my favorite. I'm all-time favorite beer. Oh,
Did this sound this silence on fuck?
Look at the one where he does it on Conan O'Brien. It was amazing. Did you see it live on Conan O'Brien?
Oh my god, you have to check this out here. Hold on. I'll grab it hang on
Yeah, that's a good worth of copyright doing that. This will blow your mind
But when they did that I mean they just fucking knocked so I'm gonna go out of the fucking park with your own song
And one more favor from you psyche, and I won't ask you for another one
Can you put this in the chat for me one more time?
This is the dessert song that they did live on Conan, and I think it's better than the original version. It's fucking okay
All right, I just downloaded it
Yeah, watch it for sure
Yeah
Did I tell you what he's got to be my fucking one of my favorite is fucking songs of all items all time. It's a good
I mean
There's been a lot of country Westerns back when I was a kid that blew it out of the pack
You know some whaling and shit like that. I love way like that, but for today's music
I've always been crazy
Been busted that's the dude. I love Wayland. He Wayland was one of my I grew up. I mean he was one of my
Awesome fucking Willie still kicking he made it to his fucking event. It's the last one he made it to I just saw him like
Four years ago at the at the screw and he was it was cool, but it was just kind of really mellow
I walked out on Garth Brooks
Hmm. I fucking walked out on guys books. All I saw was a man with a white hat and a white fucking suit
Running all over the place acting like they were on fucky crystal meth or some damn good coke
And they're gonna be made any sense and as far as fucking ZZ top all they did was stand there
And put they didn't move
I was like I went to the bar across the street on both of them
One was in fucking St. P, Florida and the other ones in Rhode Island both had bars across the street and the music was
Better listened to it from the Coliseum. Hmm. I
Got I got really no show whatsoever. It's basically Garth Brooks
You think they'd be fire and fucking all kinds of shit
I got really lucky and I got to see the Eagles and Forner and a couple other bands when I was nine years old on my dad's
It's the most amazing I used to go to a lot of shows
I followed the missus from Seattle all the way down to Southern California like I went to like six of their shows in room like
Oh, yeah, see I'm on the East Coast so I did like
Like my voice stuff fucking Rhode Island and you know
It's nice to meet you Hebrew. Yes. Nice to meet you too Mason
I actually played I actually played drums for yeah for I played drums to different bands
I listen to and stuff like that and it's called covers when he played up other like banji here and stuff like that like I
Used to play this look not a stuff like that. I played a different bands and stuff like on you got it on your
Can you can watch it? Can you play bleep?
Yeah, I don't have any
Hebrew, I don't have any videos posted on my YouTube channel because I didn't make any on there
I said I haven't got any on there yet. Can you play wait and bleed?
I know how to play wait and bleed. Yeah, but I mean it takes me a little bit of wild
It takes me a little bit of wild to warm up and get you know get it going when I'm playing to it
It's what about favorite songs
Well, what's your is that that's your favorite slipknot song though. Yeah for sure
Yeah
I'll say my favorite one is the one called the dying song. You heard the dying song?
Yeah, it's a good one. It's gonna put your hands into the water. Let your mouth go sick in
dry. That's the way it starts out. Like, you know, that's how the song starts. Oh, yeah. It's a good one.
You want to know who's kind of hard to play and like I never could master it really that I had trouble learning was a system
System of a down
Yeah, they have a weird drumming pattern
He brought no what Baylor talk about man. Yeah system of a down
He drew I gotta take off man big dog. Hey much love Tracy. Hey, you take care
Yeah, yeah appreciate it
Yeah, Tracy. I hear you. I have not seen Tracy in probably two years. So
He bro, this is my first time meeting you man
Yeah, no, that's cool. I I like meeting new people
Hey, bro, I don't think we ever met each other before, huh? This is our first day meeting each other
Yeah, I don't think we've met each other before no I
Know psyche though Hebrew like it's psyche now. We've been friends for like over a couple months. I think now
It's been a couple months or about one or two months
Yeah
What do you say? I said psyche's a good guy
Yeah, but I was gonna say who is that a picture of like on your uh, you know your
Camera thing like who's that a picture in the background? Is that you? Yeah, that's me
It looks like Chester Bittington from Lincoln Park keeper. That's who he looks like Todd
Yeah, didn't you die don't you?
Yeah, the singer from yeah, the singer from Lincoln Park. He died. You knew that right?
That's sad
he was a guy that's saying he was a guy who's saying normal in that band but the
other guy that's still live in the band that's the singer another singer he's
actually the rapper that was in that band and that he would rap in that band yeah
you knew about that Hebrew yeah I knew that Chester Benning Bennington or
Bennings yeah Chester Bennington was there's
There's two singers in the band Hebrew there's was rapper in a band as a singer
There's a regular singer in the band. I was singing screaming yelling all that when you would see
Mason you don't want to bend me over my drums. Do you?
Why would you say that I never said anything like that? Oh, so oh, that's not you
I thought it was you that said that in the chat, but it was someone else me soon. No, I'm not
That's disgusting. No, I'm not
Hey, bro, I'm not even in the chat anymore. I was before when I used to be in the chat 90 more though
someone just said it in the chat so sick them yeah I don't I don't know what's
wrong with them there must be something wrong with them huh yeah there must be
snorting that dick dust
us up here but people we're just left up here by ourselves right now you and I
It's like psych he's not here. No, I know I was thinking about porn bombing him. I'm not gonna do that
I'm just kidding. No, no, Hebrew
You're just joking maybe you have to be because you don't want to get his channel like you know taking down or strike
They're anything like that
Pardon bomb is not my style
Yeah, but it's a bad thing for his channel too though, right?
Yeah, I'm just joking
No, no
Scout
Oh my god, my dog just spilt my water all over my bed.
Oh my god.
Hebrew, are you serious?
It's alright.
It's just water at least, at least it's not like anything colored.
Damn it, Scout.
It wasn't his fault, it shouldn't have been sitting there.
You heard the new Slipknot album though, like not the newest one, but I think there's one before it, right?
The one that had the song on it, the one I told you about earlier?
I've heard it, but I don't really listen to it.
I don't really listen to Slipknot very much. I mean, I like that one album that had Wait and Bleed on it.
The Wait and Bleed? The Wait and Bleed song?
Yeah, I like that album, but I haven't really listened to that since it came out.
it's a long time ago that's a long time yeah it was a long time ago
you haven't learned to thank the fudges of my balls the pain was always frying
i'm obsessed with um lyrics like knowing lyrics and like liking lyrics so when i uh
when i say that i like a song or like i like a band or somebody i like i really like study lyrics so
yeah
Yeah, Hebrew Hebrew if I turn if I turn quiet on you. I'm not trying to turn quiet on you
I'm just doing other things right now though. So if you hear me turn quite as I'm not trying to be like that on purpose
You're fine, man. Don't worry about it. I'm okay. I'm cleaning up this water. I'm cleaning up this water real quick
I
Gotta take my my blankets off now and throw them in the washer because I don't want this to be all wet
Dang it
Scout come on. Good boy lay down. Good boy
So if you don't mind me asking like are you on the west coast or the east coast or
Mid-Mid or I don't know which one you do there Mason. Oh
Fuck me, huh? Just ignore me, huh?
I see Andrew Andrew. I mean, uh, no, hey, bro. I told you I was doing stuff, man
I'm not ignoring your purpose man. I know I was just
Are you on the east coast or west coast?
I'm on uh, uh, like the bottom of you know where the states are, you know, like where texas is and louisiana is
close to that area
Yeah, I live in, Oregon
You live in, Oregon
I stayed by Texas and I stayed by Louisiana. So I think that's like the East
South Coast, right? I think
Yeah, like southern southern. Yeah, are you like close to Katie? Oh
No, I was close to Houston though before but I stayed by Houston
But I don't say by Houston anymore though, so I moved to uh, I moved just not too long ago to uh, New Orleans
So I stayed around the New Orleans area
I stayed in Texas I stayed in Texas for a long time Hebrew, but I went to Louisiana though
So now I'm in Louisiana, and I stay around there. Do you like crawfish?
Yeah, yeah, that's okay. I'm in gumbo
Yeah gumbos. Yeah gumbos good to me
That's the place to get it
Yeah, they have it here. Yeah, yeah, the easy end is that's what they're known for
gumbo I
Stay around the New Orleans area though now like that's where I stay around right now
Do you know a youtuber named Candy Grand Prix?
No, I never heard of that
Okay, she's like a a big obese black woman that that's a homeless woman that begs for money
There's just curious cuz she's from there, too
You guys could like hook up and hang out or something
Got a girlfriend or what you married you got an old lady or what?
No
No, no, it's not like that. No, it's not like that man. I'm just doing something. I told you I'm busy
No, I don't have a girlfriend man or anything like that right now
Sounds like a VC conversation not a panel conversation. Why don't you come up and change the conversation to a panel conversation?
I don't know what to talk about
Hey Hebrew, if you want me to go I could just go like if
No, no, no, no, no, you have nothing has nothing to do with you. I'm reading the chat
And I was just okay. I don't know. I don't know what to talk about fucking psyche left. That's what I feel like
Hebrew that's what I'm saying
Like paper that's what kind of the point I'm trying to make because I'm trying to say like if I don't really have much to say
That's why I'm doing other stuff right now. He brought I'm not really just up here just to talk like right now
You can go. Yeah, you can leave if you want
Yeah, I'm just coming here to be with psyche though because psyche's my friend and stuff like that him and I we get along and stuff with each other
Well, we just met each other doesn't can't we be like friends or like nice to each other?
No, no Hebrew. I was talking about no Hebrew
I was talking about psyche though cuz psyche and I were cool and stuff like that him and I
We know each other for a while and we've been cool each other
That's cool
No, I have nothing against you though. No Hebrew. I have nothing against you man. I
Know you don't I just I know that
I'm saying it's okay. Yeah. Yeah, I'm saying it's okay like if you want to you know get to know me or talk to me
But yeah, I just I don't really have a lot to say
Right now. Did you did you play the drums in school or did you just play it on your runtime?
No, I used to play drums at home a lot
I have a drum set and I would play it at home and I would try to play this
You know like I listen to songs on the like the radio or some kind of music thing
I listen to and I try to play what I hear on the drums
Like like cover stuff like you know playing the other bands of stuff
Mason why did you go to the other channel and have psyche's channel strikes? No
No, Hebrew don't listen to what other people say like a psyche wants you to know not that I was supposed to ignore people like that
If people say stuff like that, okay
Okay, do you know what kind of drum set you have like what brand it is I had a CB
it was a I
Had a PDP drum set before Hebrew was called PDP for civic Pacific drum and percussion. Yeah, those are nice
Yeah, that's the one I had when I had one but I had to get rid of it
I told psyche about that because I had to get some I didn't have money and stuff like that
I didn't have a job or anything so I had to get rid of it so I can get money for food in a place to
Stay so I won't be homeless and stuff like that. You understand. Yeah, how many piece was it like how many pieces?
Do you know?
It was like a five piece with three different symbols like a hi-hat a crash symbol and a ride symbol
But the rest of the drums were like a snare drum a first tom a second tom and a floor tom with the bass drum
so it's like a five-piece drum set with
About a five-piece drum set
Five and then eight by any plus the symbols eight. Yeah. Yeah symbols makes it a eight piece. Yeah
Yeah, mine was yeah, I had like an 11 piece, but I had more
Okay
I miss it so much. I don't even want to talk about it kind of makes me depressed talking about mine
Sucks. Hey Hebrew, when are you gonna be back on here?
Cuz I don't think I've ever met you before until today, right? All right. Do you ever come in here other days?
Yeah, I have before just not I don't get like I don't come up on panel all the time and I
Usually stream my own I usually go live on my own channel and
Just hang out there with some people I know, but I wanted to come over here to talk to psyche about
Scorpios
Yeah, yeah, I can understand that I was curious about my sign
Uh, so um Hebrew. Yeah, it's nice to meet you man, but uh, I think I'm gonna go do something though
So like if I leave though, don't don't take it like personal though or anything
I'm not going to you're fine. It's nice to meet you man. Have a good have a good afternoon
Yeah, yeah, I hope you can come back though Hebrew come back on here. So I could talk to you again or something
Yeah, I'll be around
Just see me around
I'll let you I'll let you get back uh Hebrew, but I gotta do some stuff. So I gotta get back later though
Alright get out of here. Have a good day. Have a good one. See ya. Bye man
later
And then there was one
Psyche can I show them that funny picture that I made of you a long time ago that you got mad and kicked me for?
Do you care if I do that? I
Didn't hear a no so
Can't believe you got mad at me for that and you actually kicked me and you were like angry. It was just a joke
Can I show it? Yeah, I'll just show the fuck yeah